[
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CC", 
        "correct": "BC", 
        "incorrect": "CB", 
        "length": 2, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0408329997330665, 
        "stimulus": 1, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBA", 
        "correct": "BBA", 
        "incorrect": "BAB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9753916592266355, 
        "stimulus": 16, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBABACB", 
        "correct": "BCBABACB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBABACB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.3729368969093025, 
        "stimulus": 589, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCACAA", 
        "correct": "BCCACAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCACAA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1670651955374733, 
        "stimulus": 603, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCABB", 
        "correct": "BCCABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9923888355413062, 
        "stimulus": 807, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCB", 
        "correct": "BBBCB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.6291528696058959, 
        "stimulus": 164, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABCACBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABCACBC", 
        "correct": "BBABCACBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCABCACBC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.390494869250875, 
        "stimulus": 872, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCCACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCCACB", 
        "correct": "BCBCCACB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCCACB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2159478995106965, 
        "stimulus": 509, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCCACCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCCACCCC", 
        "correct": "BCBCCACCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCCACCCC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0937724318833117, 
        "stimulus": 766, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCB", 
        "correct": "BCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9753916592266355, 
        "stimulus": 20, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCC", 
        "correct": "BCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBC", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.5968222670425287, 
        "stimulus": 10, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABBCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBABBCBB", 
        "correct": "BCBABBCBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBABBCBB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2524715149788173, 
        "stimulus": 458, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAA", 
        "correct": "BAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCA", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.5148936210866033, 
        "stimulus": 40, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CA", 
        "correct": "BA", 
        "incorrect": "BC", 
        "length": 2, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.5590169943749475, 
        "stimulus": 15, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBAAACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBAAACA", 
        "correct": "BCBBAAACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBAAACA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0407813856553962, 
        "stimulus": 769, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCAAB", 
        "correct": "BBCAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCCAAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2811751249102934, 
        "stimulus": 668, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAB", 
        "correct": "BAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.4653002578169967, 
        "stimulus": 25, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBBABCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBBABCC", 
        "correct": "BABBBABCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBBABCC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.3771407726467748, 
        "stimulus": 515, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCBCBACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCBCBACA", 
        "correct": "BCCCBCBACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCBCBACA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2718745637806939, 
        "stimulus": 264, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCABB", 
        "correct": "BBCABB", 
        "incorrect": "BCCABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.17045606650917, 
        "stimulus": 870, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAABBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAAABBC", 
        "correct": "BAAAABBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAAABBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0323608272584777, 
        "stimulus": 241, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCC", 
        "correct": "BCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.7480269146124984, 
        "stimulus": 205, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCB", 
        "correct": "BBCB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8210137957464411, 
        "stimulus": 173, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAC", 
        "correct": "BACAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.135539447199374, 
        "stimulus": 215, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAC", 
        "correct": "BCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8939036037548898, 
        "stimulus": 48, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBBACAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBBACAC", 
        "correct": "BABBBACAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBBACAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.328488044483166, 
        "stimulus": 856, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAABAABAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCAABAABAA", 
        "correct": "BCCAABAABAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCAABAABAA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4302443174144994, 
        "stimulus": 645, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBA", 
        "correct": "BBBBA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1596981930889996, 
        "stimulus": 595, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACACABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACACABC", 
        "correct": "BAACACABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACACABC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1631347414197253, 
        "stimulus": 485, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAACBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCAACBCC", 
        "correct": "BBCAACBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCAACBCC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2649981863188025, 
        "stimulus": 411, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBC", 
        "correct": "BBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCC", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8374896350934077, 
        "stimulus": 54, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAAA", 
        "correct": "BCAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBAAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9674676475489454, 
        "stimulus": 299, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCCB", 
        "correct": "BCBCCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.5650687755383723, 
        "stimulus": 361, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCA", 
        "correct": "BABCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8980849837496987, 
        "stimulus": 715, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCCBCCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCCBCCCC", 
        "correct": "BBCCCBCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCCCBCCCC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9282637306924194, 
        "stimulus": 86, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACC", 
        "correct": "BCACC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.5714513435426471, 
        "stimulus": 67, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACAAAAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBACAAAAAA", 
        "correct": "BCBACAAAAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBACAAAAAA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9294204183519893, 
        "stimulus": 622, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBB", 
        "correct": "BBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9753916592266355, 
        "stimulus": 22, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CB", 
        "correct": "BB", 
        "incorrect": "BC", 
        "length": 2, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.14564392373896, 
        "stimulus": 0, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACBACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACBACC", 
        "correct": "BCACBACC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACBACC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2443711388615373, 
        "stimulus": 165, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABC", 
        "correct": "BABC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0765250809897557, 
        "stimulus": 143, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCBCAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCBCAAA", 
        "correct": "BACCBCAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCBCAAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2305938267397325, 
        "stimulus": 963, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAABBCABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBAABBCABC", 
        "correct": "BBBAABBCABC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBAABBCABC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1960410074708694, 
        "stimulus": 248, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCA", 
        "correct": "BCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBA", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9753916592266355, 
        "stimulus": 64, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACB", 
        "correct": "BCACB", 
        "incorrect": "CBACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.627661001921685, 
        "stimulus": 195, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCA", 
        "correct": "BCCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9455493920499229, 
        "stimulus": 36, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBC", 
        "correct": "BBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.052675163571365, 
        "stimulus": 116, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBACCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBACCCA", 
        "correct": "BABBACCCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBACCCA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.3488101605432727, 
        "stimulus": 912, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCCAAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCCAAAA", 
        "correct": "BACCCAAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCCAAAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1399321784595273, 
        "stimulus": 978, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCCB", 
        "correct": "BCCCCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.257894362992444, 
        "stimulus": 337, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAABACA", 
        "correct": "BAABACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBABACA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0954062101457, 
        "stimulus": 480, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBBA", 
        "correct": "BBBBBA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBBA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0413436206658777, 
        "stimulus": 216, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBB", 
        "correct": "BACBBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8780116586979104, 
        "stimulus": 507, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCA", 
        "correct": "BBCCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.055442245380264, 
        "stimulus": 332, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAC", 
        "correct": "BBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BABC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.7259781435998566, 
        "stimulus": 129, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACCCAACCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACCCAACCC", 
        "correct": "BCACCCAACCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACCCAACCC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0329999617140837, 
        "stimulus": 575, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACCBB", 
        "correct": "BAACCBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBACCBB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2424958340004666, 
        "stimulus": 572, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCBBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCBBAB", 
        "correct": "BBCCBBAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCCCBBAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.234162471418532, 
        "stimulus": 774, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBCCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBCCCA", 
        "correct": "BBCBCCCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCCBCCCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1792476415070754, 
        "stimulus": 380, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCC", 
        "correct": "BBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.6363961030678927, 
        "stimulus": 397, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACABC", 
        "correct": "BACABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.097789106497343, 
        "stimulus": 949, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACCABABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBACCABABB", 
        "correct": "BCBACCABABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBACCABABB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2994553354918181, 
        "stimulus": 799, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCAAC", 
        "correct": "BCCCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCAAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9413799154032958, 
        "stimulus": 225, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAC", 
        "correct": "BAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABC", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1547005383792517, 
        "stimulus": 24, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCCCAACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCCCAACA", 
        "correct": "BCBCCCAACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCCCAACA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.11477736075397, 
        "stimulus": 103, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBABB", 
        "correct": "BCCBABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBABB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9242572693355693, 
        "stimulus": 883, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBBBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBBBAC", 
        "correct": "BBCBBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBBBAC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0894062077105242, 
        "stimulus": 548, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAABABA", 
        "correct": "BAABABA", 
        "incorrect": "CBABABA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0733706357468857, 
        "stimulus": 599, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABCCABAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBABCCABAA", 
        "correct": "BCBABCCABAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBABCCABAA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4443795956437124, 
        "stimulus": 880, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBA", 
        "correct": "BBBA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9354143466934853, 
        "stimulus": 17, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBC", 
        "correct": "BCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8752777337000589, 
        "stimulus": 112, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAACAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAACAC", 
        "correct": "BAAACAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAACAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.247979695295406, 
        "stimulus": 130, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCB", 
        "correct": "BCBCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.026702804639147, 
        "stimulus": 135, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBAC", 
        "correct": "BBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9616036803364973, 
        "stimulus": 218, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBAAA", 
        "correct": "BBCBAAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCCBAAA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1946096396074677, 
        "stimulus": 646, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAB", 
        "correct": "BCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.4863780965524444, 
        "stimulus": 56, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAABCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAABCAB", 
        "correct": "BACAABCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCAABCAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2303359384855956, 
        "stimulus": 616, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBA", 
        "correct": "BCBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0733332497340673, 
        "stimulus": 11, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCABB", 
        "correct": "BCABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBABB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8422155201533773, 
        "stimulus": 149, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCA", 
        "correct": "BBCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0242380840439291, 
        "stimulus": 602, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABACCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABACCAA", 
        "correct": "BABACCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBACCAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1908817880937488, 
        "stimulus": 973, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBB", 
        "correct": "BCBBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.28284271247461906, 
        "stimulus": 261, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBACBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBACBBA", 
        "correct": "BBBACBBA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBACBBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9538089364490552, 
        "stimulus": 923, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABAABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCABAABC", 
        "correct": "BCCABAABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABAABC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1362895896890908, 
        "stimulus": 417, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCC", 
        "correct": "BBCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8514693182963201, 
        "stimulus": 401, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCACCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCACCAB", 
        "correct": "BACCACCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCACCAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2783875356706293, 
        "stimulus": 432, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBACBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBACBCB", 
        "correct": "BBBACBCB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBACBCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.3052252385646024, 
        "stimulus": 929, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCBCBC", 
        "correct": "BBBCBCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCBCBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.883522850670999, 
        "stimulus": 324, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCACBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCACBCA", 
        "correct": "BCCACBCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCACBCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1930882327940207, 
        "stimulus": 686, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBCBBBBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBCBBBBCC", 
        "correct": "BACBCBBBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBCBBBBCC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4650626978768897, 
        "stimulus": 615, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBBBC", 
        "correct": "BBBBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBBBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1169282425382536, 
        "stimulus": 34, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBCAB", 
        "correct": "BCBBCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBCAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1150868673136316, 
        "stimulus": 108, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBACA", 
        "correct": "BBBACA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBACA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9464416537214755, 
        "stimulus": 425, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBB", 
        "correct": "BCBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.7697402159170327, 
        "stimulus": 223, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCCA", 
        "correct": "BACCCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.004260340847704, 
        "stimulus": 301, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACACAACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACACAACC", 
        "correct": "BBACACAACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACACAACC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2667740502231553, 
        "stimulus": 901, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAB", 
        "correct": "BAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.4863780965524444, 
        "stimulus": 26, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCAAC", 
        "correct": "BCCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCAAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.895457677932456, 
        "stimulus": 57, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAA", 
        "correct": "BBAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9204285158587705, 
        "stimulus": 38, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACC", 
        "correct": "BACC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9282045317741014, 
        "stimulus": 30, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABAAAA", 
        "correct": "BABAAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBAAAA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.002565445073452, 
        "stimulus": 327, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCABBBC", 
        "correct": "BCABBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBABBBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9884450244008107, 
        "stimulus": 832, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCACC", 
        "correct": "BCBCACC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCACC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0219390443812384, 
        "stimulus": 59, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBB", 
        "correct": "BBBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.7697402159170327, 
        "stimulus": 448, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACB", 
        "correct": "BBACB", 
        "incorrect": "BABCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.65, 
        "stimulus": 569, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAACABABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAACABABC", 
        "correct": "BBAACABABC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAACABABC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.261252335620833, 
        "stimulus": 212, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBCACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBCACA", 
        "correct": "BCBBCACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBCACA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0787831793961882, 
        "stimulus": 992, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCB", 
        "correct": "BCCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9834574992372467, 
        "stimulus": 2, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCABBAB", 
        "correct": "BCCABBAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABBAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2722414476112407, 
        "stimulus": 796, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAACCCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAACCCBB", 
        "correct": "BCAACCCBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAACCCBB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1851422337413897, 
        "stimulus": 450, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCACAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCACAC", 
        "correct": "BBCACAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCACAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0635290801423296, 
        "stimulus": 190, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBB", 
        "correct": "BABBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.4544850250962032, 
        "stimulus": 114, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABAB", 
        "correct": "BABAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0220966872251847, 
        "stimulus": 283, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACCCA", 
        "correct": "BBACCCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCACCCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0814923056032557, 
        "stimulus": 918, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCB", 
        "correct": "BCCCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9287087810503356, 
        "stimulus": 226, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACA", 
        "correct": "BBACA", 
        "incorrect": "BABCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1732256105853358, 
        "stimulus": 905, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCCC", 
        "correct": "BCCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2596565777534572, 
        "stimulus": 315, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCACCACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCACCACB", 
        "correct": "BCCACCACB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCACCACB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8864419445105554, 
        "stimulus": 592, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAACCBABAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAACCBABAC", 
        "correct": "BCAACCBABAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAACCBABAC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2139638116024312, 
        "stimulus": 755, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACBC", 
        "correct": "BAACBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9923888355413062, 
        "stimulus": 624, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCBC", 
        "correct": "BCBCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8377645789814215, 
        "stimulus": 704, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABA", 
        "correct": "BABA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.4863780965524444, 
        "stimulus": 5, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAB", 
        "correct": "BBAB", 
        "incorrect": "BABB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9354143466934853, 
        "stimulus": 229, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCACC", 
        "correct": "BABCACC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCACC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9482798605251253, 
        "stimulus": 847, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBBBAABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBBBAABC", 
        "correct": "BBBBBBAABC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBBBAABC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4502799422641939, 
        "stimulus": 581, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBCA", 
        "correct": "BCBBCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0177474689111268, 
        "stimulus": 340, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCCABBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCCABBC", 
        "correct": "BACCCABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCCABBC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0560123280705755, 
        "stimulus": 310, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCB", 
        "correct": "BBCCB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9616036803364973, 
        "stimulus": 683, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBC", 
        "correct": "BACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.736237555507327, 
        "stimulus": 146, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBC", 
        "correct": "BBCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9046177830074609, 
        "stimulus": 792, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBA", 
        "correct": "BACBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0649500688078717, 
        "stimulus": 560, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBA", 
        "correct": "BABBA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0414805029556227, 
        "stimulus": 497, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCBBCBBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCBBCBBAC", 
        "correct": "BBCCBBCBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCCBBCBBAC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2977060590219112, 
        "stimulus": 764, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABAA", 
        "correct": "BABAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9405751634168833, 
        "stimulus": 27, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAAABB", 
        "correct": "BBAAABB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBAABB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8588327713479313, 
        "stimulus": 12, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACC", 
        "correct": "BBACC", 
        "incorrect": "BABCC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0613937243250955, 
        "stimulus": 718, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAAA", 
        "correct": "BBAAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0471190635898735, 
        "stimulus": 152, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCAACBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCABCAACBA", 
        "correct": "BCABCAACBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBABCAACBA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4143172156709063, 
        "stimulus": 121, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBC", 
        "correct": "BCCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1056672193747992, 
        "stimulus": 44, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBABCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBABCAB", 
        "correct": "BACBABCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBABCAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1095603242784404, 
        "stimulus": 904, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAACAAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAAACAAAB", 
        "correct": "BAAAACAAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAAACAAAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2016473464030475, 
        "stimulus": 958, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAACBCBBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAACBCBBAB", 
        "correct": "BAAACBCBBAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAACBCBBAB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.3669420691739473, 
        "stimulus": 91, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAAAB", 
        "correct": "BAAAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCAAAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2389805870688009, 
        "stimulus": 125, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCB", 
        "correct": "BABCB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.7526995669167723, 
        "stimulus": 153, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABAAAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAABAAAAC", 
        "correct": "BAABAAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBABAAAAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1458398795413882, 
        "stimulus": 617, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBCB", 
        "correct": "BBCBCB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0400981387936408, 
        "stimulus": 732, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBC", 
        "correct": "BABBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8181240629557499, 
        "stimulus": 66, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBAA", 
        "correct": "BBBBAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2596565777534572, 
        "stimulus": 881, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAAABB", 
        "correct": "BCAAABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAAABB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.6517113225158607, 
        "stimulus": 257, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCBB", 
        "correct": "BCBCBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.5833333333333335, 
        "stimulus": 320, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABAC", 
        "correct": "BABAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9348573866282138, 
        "stimulus": 230, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAABBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAABBC", 
        "correct": "BCAABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAABBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9556491543042608, 
        "stimulus": 393, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBAB", 
        "correct": "BACBAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0309998064534394, 
        "stimulus": 294, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAB", 
        "correct": "BACAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.65, 
        "stimulus": 240, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBCCBB", 
        "correct": "BABBCCBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBCCBB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9658672969917895, 
        "stimulus": 642, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBB", 
        "correct": "BBCBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0762124476083819, 
        "stimulus": 55, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCAABC", 
        "correct": "BBCAABC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCAABC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0672063687933615, 
        "stimulus": 410, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAABBB", 
        "correct": "BAABBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCABBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8780116586979104, 
        "stimulus": 518, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABCBB", 
        "correct": "BBABCBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCABCBB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.100200860574858, 
        "stimulus": 422, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBCBBC", 
        "correct": "BABBCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBCBBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2033164846684814, 
        "stimulus": 266, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCACCBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCACCBAC", 
        "correct": "BACCACCBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCACCBAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1779918955546047, 
        "stimulus": 262, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBAAA", 
        "correct": "BCBAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBAAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.803218790361884, 
        "stimulus": 499, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAABCBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAABCBCC", 
        "correct": "BCAABCBCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAABCBCC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2389934014835402, 
        "stimulus": 689, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCC", 
        "correct": "BCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2382783747337809, 
        "stimulus": 345, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACABAACBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACABAACBA", 
        "correct": "BACABAACBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABAACBA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2075948401677192, 
        "stimulus": 529, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAAC", 
        "correct": "BAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.035964914803278, 
        "stimulus": 89, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACCAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACCAAA", 
        "correct": "BCACCAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBACCAAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.228692957204285, 
        "stimulus": 562, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCCBCACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCCBCACA", 
        "correct": "BCCCCBCACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCCBCACA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2860541373981023, 
        "stimulus": 303, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCACABABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCACABABB", 
        "correct": "BCCACABABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCACABABB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4097862032094504, 
        "stimulus": 461, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACAACAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACAACAC", 
        "correct": "BAACAACAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACAACAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0345998966818477, 
        "stimulus": 193, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCCCCABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCCCCABA", 
        "correct": "BABCCCCABA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCCCCABA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2439231386502752, 
        "stimulus": 989, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABACC", 
        "correct": "BBABACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCABACC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8835426847283393, 
        "stimulus": 300, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCAA", 
        "correct": "BCCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0511421878384914, 
        "stimulus": 235, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCCACCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCCACCCB", 
        "correct": "BBBCCACCCB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCCACCCB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1364005675816957, 
        "stimulus": 771, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACBA", 
        "correct": "BAACBA", 
        "incorrect": "BCACBA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8630123112871024, 
        "stimulus": 962, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACCBC", 
        "correct": "BBACCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACCBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8214285714285715, 
        "stimulus": 362, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABBCACBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAABBCACBCB", 
        "correct": "BAABBCACBCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBABBCACBCB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.444223424862045, 
        "stimulus": 739, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBABCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBABCBB", 
        "correct": "BBBABCBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBABCBB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.194060823408925, 
        "stimulus": 899, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAABAAB", 
        "correct": "BAABAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBABAAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1670651955374733, 
        "stimulus": 611, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCC", 
        "correct": "BBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0792310148125532, 
        "stimulus": 251, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABACCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABACCAB", 
        "correct": "BABACCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBACCAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1629442863978077, 
        "stimulus": 69, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAAB", 
        "correct": "BCAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1946713285809338, 
        "stimulus": 46, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBACB", 
        "correct": "BCBBACB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBACB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0484032902959226, 
        "stimulus": 233, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBBCBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBBCBBB", 
        "correct": "BBBBBCBBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBBCBBB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.5322036647193823, 
        "stimulus": 232, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABB", 
        "correct": "BBABB", 
        "incorrect": "BABBB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.7962150044638279, 
        "stimulus": 9, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAA", 
        "correct": "BAAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCAA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8103925660512387, 
        "stimulus": 275, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBBACBAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBBACBAA", 
        "correct": "BACBBBACBAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBBACBAA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.5210284017276854, 
        "stimulus": 917, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACA", 
        "correct": "BACA", 
        "incorrect": "BCCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.7204607225976853, 
        "stimulus": 3, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACC", 
        "correct": "BAACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.4544850250962032, 
        "stimulus": 203, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCCC", 
        "correct": "BACCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8203646256950535, 
        "stimulus": 761, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBBACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBBACAA", 
        "correct": "BBBBBACAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBBACAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0357924898436748, 
        "stimulus": 408, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACABA", 
        "correct": "BCACABA", 
        "incorrect": "CBACABA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2575974730637691, 
        "stimulus": 154, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAA", 
        "correct": "BCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBAA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.7204607225976853, 
        "stimulus": 71, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAACBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAACBBC", 
        "correct": "BBAACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAACBBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0910246788592963, 
        "stimulus": 824, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBCCBBCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBCCBBCBB", 
        "correct": "BBCBCCBBCBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCCBCCBBCBB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2446616346674881, 
        "stimulus": 707, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABCB", 
        "correct": "BBABCB", 
        "incorrect": "BABBCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8120954189206594, 
        "stimulus": 785, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCACACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCACACB", 
        "correct": "BCCACACB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCACACB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9132038666502088, 
        "stimulus": 951, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCA", 
        "correct": "BACCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8381527307120106, 
        "stimulus": 179, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACAAB", 
        "correct": "BAACAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBACAAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1077109579049578, 
        "stimulus": 556, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBABBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBABBA", 
        "correct": "BBBBABBA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBABBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9198178160999138, 
        "stimulus": 269, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAABBBAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAABBBAA", 
        "correct": "BBAABBBAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCAABBBAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1132791348528748, 
        "stimulus": 545, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBAC", 
        "correct": "BACBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.145495378945262, 
        "stimulus": 295, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBBB", 
        "correct": "BCCBBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0684192195410973, 
        "stimulus": 119, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACB", 
        "correct": "BACB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0616914112895417, 
        "stimulus": 436, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBB", 
        "correct": "BACBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0792310148125532, 
        "stimulus": 220, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACAB", 
        "correct": "BCACAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBACAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.7940953373531864, 
        "stimulus": 676, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCA", 
        "correct": "BCBCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.6601767440112787, 
        "stimulus": 290, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACBACCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBACBACCAC", 
        "correct": "BCBACBACCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBACBACCAC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.469559582500933, 
        "stimulus": 356, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBBAAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBBAAAB", 
        "correct": "BACBBBAAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBBAAAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.378342755266471, 
        "stimulus": 136, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCCBC", 
        "correct": "BCBCCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCCBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9180283858809201, 
        "stimulus": 291, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBACC", 
        "correct": "BBBBACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBACC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2513655205699863, 
        "stimulus": 911, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCC", 
        "correct": "BACCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.4290182257628415, 
        "stimulus": 304, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBBAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBBAAA", 
        "correct": "BCCBBAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBAAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1024660137226245, 
        "stimulus": 910, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBC", 
        "correct": "BBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9607939425287819, 
        "stimulus": 280, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBACBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBACBAB", 
        "correct": "BACBBACBAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBACBAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.400104705564232, 
        "stimulus": 974, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAABBAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAAABBAAC", 
        "correct": "BBAAABBAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAAABBAAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2004843919478971, 
        "stimulus": 196, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAABABCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAABABCC", 
        "correct": "BAAABABCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAABABCC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0863284601696597, 
        "stimulus": 658, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABABBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAABABBA", 
        "correct": "BAABABBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBABABBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.754998773607049, 
        "stimulus": 101, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAACABBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAACABBCA", 
        "correct": "BBAACABBCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCAACABBCA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.3200892657508505, 
        "stimulus": 90, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBA", 
        "correct": "BCCBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0606601717798214, 
        "stimulus": 126, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABCC", 
        "correct": "BBABCC", 
        "incorrect": "BABBCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.6560593206407075, 
        "stimulus": 189, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBBC", 
        "correct": "BCCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9976155404671846, 
        "stimulus": 896, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABABB", 
        "correct": "BABABB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8491277003456331, 
        "stimulus": 201, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACBACBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACBACBC", 
        "correct": "BAACBACBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACBACBC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2324972658601885, 
        "stimulus": 138, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBBB", 
        "correct": "BABBBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.5783619550250588, 
        "stimulus": 808, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCAC", 
        "correct": "BBCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9163322463814376, 
        "stimulus": 19, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACABBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACABBBA", 
        "correct": "BACABBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABBBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9993865575792743, 
        "stimulus": 758, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBACBAACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBACBAACA", 
        "correct": "BCCBACBAACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBACBAACA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2580106609257151, 
        "stimulus": 708, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCBACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBCBACAA", 
        "correct": "BABBCBACAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBCBACAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4276238156015164, 
        "stimulus": 915, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBBBCABBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBBBCABBA", 
        "correct": "BCBBBBCABBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBBBCABBA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4182129553535234, 
        "stimulus": 169, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAACCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAACCBA", 
        "correct": "BAAACCBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBAACCBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.010001509776138, 
        "stimulus": 182, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCBAC", 
        "correct": "BBBCBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCBAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9902177635873555, 
        "stimulus": 298, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABB", 
        "correct": "BABB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9780407214456762, 
        "stimulus": 21, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABACCACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABACCACB", 
        "correct": "BBABACCACB", 
        "incorrect": "BCABACCACB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2329917960287, 
        "stimulus": 633, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAACBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBAACBAB", 
        "correct": "BCBAACBAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBAACBAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1708619170463914, 
        "stimulus": 82, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAABCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAABCCA", 
        "correct": "BCAABCCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBAABCCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2130250374457041, 
        "stimulus": 87, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBACCC", 
        "correct": "BCBACCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBACCC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8502533969366235, 
        "stimulus": 889, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBACBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBACBA", 
        "correct": "BACBACBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBACBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1845951634055412, 
        "stimulus": 784, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBACAABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBACAABB", 
        "correct": "BCCBACAABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBACAABB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2528626795815967, 
        "stimulus": 185, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBBABAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBBABAAB", 
        "correct": "BCBBBABAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBBABAAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.3056978010606801, 
        "stimulus": 979, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCBB", 
        "correct": "BBCCBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.103861911488413, 
        "stimulus": 440, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBABB", 
        "correct": "BBBABB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8996221885878242, 
        "stimulus": 385, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACAA", 
        "correct": "BBACAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCACAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.871489331435601, 
        "stimulus": 873, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBCBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBCBBC", 
        "correct": "BACBCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBCBBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1091477192763837, 
        "stimulus": 661, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAABCCBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAAABCCBCC", 
        "correct": "BAAAABCCBCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAAABCCBCC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4367828053675975, 
        "stimulus": 6, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAABCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAABCC", 
        "correct": "BCAABCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAABCC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.2299636021959177, 
        "stimulus": 853, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCBBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBCBBBB", 
        "correct": "BABBCBBBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBCBBBB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8314767980419018, 
        "stimulus": 714, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCABBC", 
        "correct": "BCABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBABBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9908157634133063, 
        "stimulus": 273, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAAABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABAAABC", 
        "correct": "BABAAABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBAAABC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1456043032750527, 
        "stimulus": 823, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACABB", 
        "correct": "BACABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.9643169254437192, 
        "stimulus": 867, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCBBACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCBBACAA", 
        "correct": "BCBCBBACAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCBBACAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.4792580873731376, 
        "stimulus": 286, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCACBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCACBB", 
        "correct": "BBCACBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCCACBB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.0939595280354717, 
        "stimulus": 940, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCAC", 
        "correct": "BBCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8274549160145807, 
        "stimulus": 813, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAACBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAAACBA", 
        "correct": "BCAAACBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBAAACBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 0.8029171351552574, 
        "stimulus": 922, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBBCACAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBBCACAC", 
        "correct": "BBCBBCACAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCBBCACAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.1257574642369128, 
        "stimulus": 719, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBBAAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBBAAAC", 
        "correct": "BCCBBAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBAAAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<C=<B", 
        "score": 1.3496492162294385, 
        "stimulus": 582, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "B", 
        "correct": "BC", 
        "incorrect": "CB", 
        "length": 2, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9428090415820634, 
        "stimulus": 1000, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBBAB", 
        "correct": "ACBBBABC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBBBACB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1948284321903655, 
        "stimulus": 1967, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAB", 
        "correct": "ACABC", 
        "incorrect": "ACACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2570787221094177, 
        "stimulus": 1141, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AC", 
        "correct": "ACC", 
        "incorrect": "CAC", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.894427190999916, 
        "stimulus": 1060, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BB", 
        "correct": "BBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1313708498984762, 
        "stimulus": 1011, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAB", 
        "correct": "CCABC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8301130370744624, 
        "stimulus": 1405, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCB", 
        "correct": "BABCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BABCCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.559563715162477, 
        "stimulus": 1848, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBAB", 
        "correct": "ABBABC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBACB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9279640295100132, 
        "stimulus": 1658, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "A", 
        "correct": "AC", 
        "incorrect": "CA", 
        "length": 2, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9428090415820634, 
        "stimulus": 1007, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBA", 
        "correct": "CCBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7794298288469034, 
        "stimulus": 1444, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BA", 
        "correct": "BAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCA", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1480205929819904, 
        "stimulus": 1042, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AB", 
        "correct": "ABC", 
        "incorrect": "ACB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1480205929819904, 
        "stimulus": 1091, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BC", 
        "correct": "BCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBC", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.894427190999916, 
        "stimulus": 1050, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAC", 
        "correct": "CAACC", 
        "incorrect": "CACAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9428090415820634, 
        "stimulus": 1562, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACC", 
        "correct": "BACCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3849067558120454, 
        "stimulus": 1348, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABCBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCBCB", 
        "correct": "BABCBCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BABCBCCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3419333563908318, 
        "stimulus": 1794, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAA", 
        "correct": "AAAC", 
        "incorrect": "AACA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2121830534626528, 
        "stimulus": 1014, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBCABBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCABBBC", 
        "correct": "CCBCABBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCABBCBC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0448493563559746, 
        "stimulus": 1488, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCC", 
        "correct": "BCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9035079029052512, 
        "stimulus": 1071, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBCCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBCCCB", 
        "correct": "BBBCCCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBBCCBCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.211060630662868, 
        "stimulus": 1239, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAC", 
        "correct": "AACC", 
        "incorrect": "ACAC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0301575072754254, 
        "stimulus": 1260, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCAC", 
        "correct": "ACCCACC", 
        "incorrect": "ACCCCCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0204134702198013, 
        "stimulus": 1114, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAC", 
        "correct": "CACC", 
        "incorrect": "CCAC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8081220356417685, 
        "stimulus": 1164, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAAACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAAACB", 
        "correct": "ACAAACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACAAACCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0670749549979297, 
        "stimulus": 1815, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACCBB", 
        "correct": "BACCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BACCBCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2478580447023262, 
        "stimulus": 1831, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBB", 
        "correct": "BBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2121830534626528, 
        "stimulus": 1211, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABACBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABACBC", 
        "correct": "BABACBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BABACCBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3900093080235916, 
        "stimulus": 1400, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AA", 
        "correct": "AAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACA", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1313708498984762, 
        "stimulus": 1023, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CA", 
        "correct": "CAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCA", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.894427190999916, 
        "stimulus": 1021, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBC", 
        "correct": "BBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0301575072754254, 
        "stimulus": 1037, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACB", 
        "correct": "ACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9591920992658123, 
        "stimulus": 999, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACABC", 
        "correct": "ACABCC", 
        "incorrect": "ACACBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1865332999420617, 
        "stimulus": 1225, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAAAB", 
        "correct": "BAAABC", 
        "incorrect": "BAAACB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2237192493158084, 
        "stimulus": 1508, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCCA", 
        "correct": "BCCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCACC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7496555682941201, 
        "stimulus": 1138, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBA", 
        "correct": "BBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8984041307564036, 
        "stimulus": 1016, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBBBBBCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBBBBBCBA", 
        "correct": "ABBBBBBCBAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBBBBCBCA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.408528374632277, 
        "stimulus": 1482, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCB", 
        "correct": "CCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7782664685987215, 
        "stimulus": 1156, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBCABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCABC", 
        "correct": "CCBCABCC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCACBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.119954914337298, 
        "stimulus": 1542, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCBCCAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBCCAAC", 
        "correct": "CBCBCCAACC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBCCACAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4616091327978835, 
        "stimulus": 1910, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABC", 
        "correct": "BABCC", 
        "incorrect": "BACBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.6333324636149358, 
        "stimulus": 1193, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCA", 
        "correct": "CCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.6649617087277087, 
        "stimulus": 1113, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CB", 
        "correct": "CBC", 
        "incorrect": "CCB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.984723147373133, 
        "stimulus": 1004, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBC", 
        "correct": "CBCC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9823785858828832, 
        "stimulus": 1018, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCCC", 
        "correct": "ACCCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CACCCCC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.93580962004588, 
        "stimulus": 1607, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACAAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAAAA", 
        "correct": "CACAAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CACAAACA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1461334153502802, 
        "stimulus": 1612, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCCABBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCABBB", 
        "correct": "CCCCABBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CCCCABBCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5224207284372662, 
        "stimulus": 1861, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBAAC", 
        "correct": "CBBAACC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBACAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3928969519790342, 
        "stimulus": 1267, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAABCCABAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAABCCABAB", 
        "correct": "AAABCCABABC", 
        "incorrect": "AAABCCABACB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3050884823357602, 
        "stimulus": 1518, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCC", 
        "correct": "CCBCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CCCCBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7398514417902535, 
        "stimulus": 1073, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAACCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAACCAC", 
        "correct": "AAACCACC", 
        "incorrect": "AAACCCAC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3072748716337148, 
        "stimulus": 1076, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACCBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACCBAB", 
        "correct": "AACCBABC", 
        "incorrect": "AACCBACB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0613371234446767, 
        "stimulus": 1918, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABACABABBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACABABBC", 
        "correct": "ABACABABBCC", 
        "incorrect": "ABACABABCBC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4645075711847495, 
        "stimulus": 1592, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAACAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAACAB", 
        "correct": "BCAACABC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAACACB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3208557564568755, 
        "stimulus": 1977, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABA", 
        "correct": "AABAC", 
        "incorrect": "AABCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.5751951978601728, 
        "stimulus": 1059, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBA", 
        "correct": "CBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9026327115375886, 
        "stimulus": 1388, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBB", 
        "correct": "CBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1154144443730543, 
        "stimulus": 1067, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABBBBBCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABBBBBCAA", 
        "correct": "BABBBBBCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BABBBBBCACA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5681781892812385, 
        "stimulus": 1273, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAC", 
        "correct": "BACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.204722354448267, 
        "stimulus": 1022, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCABB", 
        "correct": "ACCABBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACCABCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2507666837607143, 
        "stimulus": 1148, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAABCBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAABCBAC", 
        "correct": "BCAABCBACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAABCBCAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4952365569302146, 
        "stimulus": 1798, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAA", 
        "correct": "CAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CAACA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.119702400755972, 
        "stimulus": 1132, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAA", 
        "correct": "BAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BACA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.101373060308832, 
        "stimulus": 1012, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBAC", 
        "correct": "CCBACC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8347065795168704, 
        "stimulus": 1216, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABABA", 
        "correct": "BABABAC", 
        "incorrect": "BABABCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4889462736442576, 
        "stimulus": 1836, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBAC", 
        "correct": "ACBACC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBCAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.5473607044671857, 
        "stimulus": 1465, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACACABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACACABA", 
        "correct": "BACACABAC", 
        "incorrect": "BACACABCA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4324901616177155, 
        "stimulus": 1962, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAA", 
        "correct": "CAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CACA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9981756028243807, 
        "stimulus": 1107, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCA", 
        "correct": "CCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CACC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9591920992658123, 
        "stimulus": 1232, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCCCBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCCCBAC", 
        "correct": "BCCCCBACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCCCBCAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9203470055860264, 
        "stimulus": 1171, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACAB", 
        "correct": "CBACABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACACB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3238653290153046, 
        "stimulus": 1546, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABA", 
        "correct": "ABAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0661695771284148, 
        "stimulus": 1098, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAABBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAABBC", 
        "correct": "AAABBCC", 
        "incorrect": "AAABCBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.196894917685096, 
        "stimulus": 1782, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABA", 
        "correct": "CABAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.273479517031985, 
        "stimulus": 1027, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAABA", 
        "correct": "CAAABAC", 
        "incorrect": "CAAABCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.238281773762611, 
        "stimulus": 1749, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAAB", 
        "correct": "AAABC", 
        "incorrect": "AAACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2379858979579041, 
        "stimulus": 1529, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAACBCABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAACBCABB", 
        "correct": "BAACBCABBC", 
        "incorrect": "BAACBCABCB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3989301592883239, 
        "stimulus": 1554, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACABBCAACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACABBCAACB", 
        "correct": "ACABBCAACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACABBCAACCB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5240060613348858, 
        "stimulus": 1801, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAA", 
        "correct": "ABAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABACA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.006119613234545, 
        "stimulus": 1597, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACACACABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACACACABC", 
        "correct": "ACACACABCC", 
        "incorrect": "ACACACACBC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5103815869026311, 
        "stimulus": 1705, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABCBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABCBAC", 
        "correct": "AABCBACC", 
        "incorrect": "AABCBCAC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3246460065680132, 
        "stimulus": 1648, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAAC", 
        "correct": "CCAACC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8082290503824867, 
        "stimulus": 1064, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBB", 
        "correct": "BBCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCBCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.880261366804629, 
        "stimulus": 1978, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCACCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACCC", 
        "correct": "BCACCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCACCC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2288046778308703, 
        "stimulus": 1559, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCABA", 
        "correct": "CBCABAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9987292616633694, 
        "stimulus": 1756, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBB", 
        "correct": "BCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7458734212276418, 
        "stimulus": 1884, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAA", 
        "correct": "ACAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACACA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7458734212276418, 
        "stimulus": 1757, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAC", 
        "correct": "CCACC", 
        "incorrect": "CACCC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8012336167697753, 
        "stimulus": 1489, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACCBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACCBCC", 
        "correct": "BACCBCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BACCCBCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3286194253580699, 
        "stimulus": 1460, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAB", 
        "correct": "CBABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.035274972520742, 
        "stimulus": 1663, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAACCCBCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAACCCBCCB", 
        "correct": "BAACCCBCCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BAACCCBCCCB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4604921788253689, 
        "stimulus": 1779, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACABCBCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACABCBCBC", 
        "correct": "BACABCBCBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BACABCBCCBC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3703161622649322, 
        "stimulus": 1015, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBACC", 
        "correct": "BBACCC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCACC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.979601156535279, 
        "stimulus": 1150, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCBACCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBACCBA", 
        "correct": "ABCBACCBAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBACCBCA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2462047984888613, 
        "stimulus": 1737, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAAACCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAAACCB", 
        "correct": "ABAAACCBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABAAACCCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3946704914829389, 
        "stimulus": 1224, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBB", 
        "correct": "CBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0661695771284148, 
        "stimulus": 1192, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBBACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBACB", 
        "correct": "CCBBACBC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBBACCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4047733854336069, 
        "stimulus": 1464, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBCA", 
        "correct": "CCBBCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBBCCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9179586431922757, 
        "stimulus": 1675, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCCCCABCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCCCABCA", 
        "correct": "CCCCCCABCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCCCCCABCCA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.254533377657392, 
        "stimulus": 1151, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACACAA", 
        "correct": "ACACAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACACACA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.2369018732101545, 
        "stimulus": 1729, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBBBA", 
        "correct": "ABBBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBBCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3659046639996648, 
        "stimulus": 1789, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCCC", 
        "correct": "BCCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.157915621136179, 
        "stimulus": 1733, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCA", 
        "correct": "BCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9591920992658123, 
        "stimulus": 1045, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABB", 
        "correct": "CBABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBABCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0437319905356648, 
        "stimulus": 1222, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBACCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBACCBB", 
        "correct": "CBBACCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBACCBCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4368102033061598, 
        "stimulus": 1847, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACAAABACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACAAABACA", 
        "correct": "AACAAABACAC", 
        "incorrect": "AACAAABACCA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3927614691432235, 
        "stimulus": 1957, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAAC", 
        "correct": "BAACC", 
        "incorrect": "BACAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8922845610362345, 
        "stimulus": 1799, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCC", 
        "correct": "CACCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.022605147302981, 
        "stimulus": 1212, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACA", 
        "correct": "BACAC", 
        "incorrect": "BACCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.035274972520742, 
        "stimulus": 1028, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABCC", 
        "correct": "CBABCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACBCC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4592787782378414, 
        "stimulus": 1857, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCC", 
        "correct": "BBCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.006119613234545, 
        "stimulus": 1615, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAAAA", 
        "correct": "BAAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BAAACA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9669926703678359, 
        "stimulus": 1468, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBAAA", 
        "correct": "BBAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBAACA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9471633575499299, 
        "stimulus": 1449, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACABCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACABCC", 
        "correct": "CACABCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CACACBCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0670118286963886, 
        "stimulus": 1667, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBBB", 
        "correct": "BBCBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCBBCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7535720729571449, 
        "stimulus": 1769, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABB", 
        "correct": "ABBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.101373060308832, 
        "stimulus": 1048, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABBBBBBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBBBBBCA", 
        "correct": "CABBBBBBCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABBBBBBCCA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.397802416301958, 
        "stimulus": 1202, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCBB", 
        "correct": "ABBCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCBCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0750962957278662, 
        "stimulus": 1821, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCA", 
        "correct": "ABCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1290230757516817, 
        "stimulus": 1622, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBABC", 
        "correct": "BCBABCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBACBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8808837310926686, 
        "stimulus": 1413, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACBBABCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBABCCB", 
        "correct": "CACBBABCCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CACBBABCCCB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.389471736631177, 
        "stimulus": 1406, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAACACABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACACABA", 
        "correct": "CAACACABAC", 
        "incorrect": "CAACACABCA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3481421462617649, 
        "stimulus": 1811, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAABB", 
        "correct": "AAABBC", 
        "incorrect": "AAABCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3288925678065202, 
        "stimulus": 1384, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABC", 
        "correct": "AABCC", 
        "incorrect": "AACBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3479777102981014, 
        "stimulus": 1682, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCA", 
        "correct": "BCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7027283689263065, 
        "stimulus": 1163, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBABCCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBABCCAC", 
        "correct": "BCBABCCACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBABCCCAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3549182369650266, 
        "stimulus": 1795, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCCBCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCBCAC", 
        "correct": "ABCCBCACC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCBCCAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.238975894409802, 
        "stimulus": 1854, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBB", 
        "correct": "CABBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CABBCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.2814007725523371, 
        "stimulus": 1355, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBB", 
        "correct": "BBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7411195299118166, 
        "stimulus": 1055, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCACAA", 
        "correct": "BCCACAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCACACA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2649565980223307, 
        "stimulus": 1735, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAB", 
        "correct": "CABC", 
        "incorrect": "CACB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1731529840973391, 
        "stimulus": 1110, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAACACABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAACACABA", 
        "correct": "BCAACACABAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAACACABCA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3859888654256711, 
        "stimulus": 1189, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBB", 
        "correct": "ACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0835156798434824, 
        "stimulus": 1213, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAB", 
        "correct": "AABC", 
        "incorrect": "AACB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9106698677405053, 
        "stimulus": 1081, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBC", 
        "correct": "BBCBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCCBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2875927598042853, 
        "stimulus": 1390, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABC", 
        "correct": "CABCC", 
        "incorrect": "CACBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9909248984623453, 
        "stimulus": 1979, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCACC", 
        "correct": "CBCACCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCACC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0274559952088915, 
        "stimulus": 1077, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBC", 
        "correct": "CBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.027717179997083, 
        "stimulus": 1374, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABABBAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABABBAAC", 
        "correct": "CBABABBAACC", 
        "incorrect": "CBABABBACAC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5195297793383404, 
        "stimulus": 1432, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCCCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCCCAA", 
        "correct": "ABBCCCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCCCACA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4472351456555457, 
        "stimulus": 1165, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACCBCABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCBCABA", 
        "correct": "CACCBCABAC", 
        "incorrect": "CACCBCABCA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4458236790907784, 
        "stimulus": 1575, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABCCA", 
        "correct": "AABCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "AABCCCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8859447821533546, 
        "stimulus": 1372, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAAABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAAAABC", 
        "correct": "BAAAABCC", 
        "incorrect": "BAAAACBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7085494183284338, 
        "stimulus": 1791, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABCAB", 
        "correct": "CBABCABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBABCACB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0210834759216474, 
        "stimulus": 1443, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACCB", 
        "correct": "CBACCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACCCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0467569016504084, 
        "stimulus": 1408, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAB", 
        "correct": "CAABC", 
        "incorrect": "CAACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7794298288469034, 
        "stimulus": 1818, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABBC", 
        "correct": "AABBCC", 
        "incorrect": "AABCBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3168818732052172, 
        "stimulus": 1378, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBC", 
        "correct": "BBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8922845610362345, 
        "stimulus": 1556, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACAABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAABA", 
        "correct": "CACAABAC", 
        "incorrect": "CACAABCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.227085971874215, 
        "stimulus": 1035, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCC", 
        "correct": "CABCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CACBCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1063820478490292, 
        "stimulus": 1346, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCCBABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCCBABB", 
        "correct": "BCCCBABBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCCBABCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.349710003929419, 
        "stimulus": 1117, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACBCABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACBCABC", 
        "correct": "CBACBCABCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACBCACBC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.466413021615352, 
        "stimulus": 1422, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABCAC", 
        "correct": "AABCACC", 
        "incorrect": "AABCCAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3246794863033091, 
        "stimulus": 1289, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBABCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBABCAA", 
        "correct": "ACBABCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBABCACA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0985020386881532, 
        "stimulus": 1810, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACA", 
        "correct": "BCACAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2237192493158084, 
        "stimulus": 1722, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACBBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACBBBC", 
        "correct": "BACBBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BACBBCBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.5496376319448053, 
        "stimulus": 1951, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABACCCACCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACCCACCA", 
        "correct": "ABACCCACCAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABACCCACCCA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3827438216064463, 
        "stimulus": 1938, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCABBA", 
        "correct": "CCABBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCABBCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3520130623557836, 
        "stimulus": 1522, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAB", 
        "correct": "BABC", 
        "incorrect": "BACB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1372854731624298, 
        "stimulus": 1133, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACC", 
        "correct": "ACCC", 
        "incorrect": "CACC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9035079029052512, 
        "stimulus": 1129, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABB", 
        "correct": "CABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2432950024167977, 
        "stimulus": 1065, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAACCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAACCAA", 
        "correct": "BCAACCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAACCACA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2170148419968652, 
        "stimulus": 1312, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABACBCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABACBCAA", 
        "correct": "CBABACBCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBABACBCACA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3762074057114575, 
        "stimulus": 1606, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBAABB", 
        "correct": "BBAABBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBAABCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2009343041595508, 
        "stimulus": 1509, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCABB", 
        "correct": "CCABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CCABCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1097153706889848, 
        "stimulus": 1853, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBCABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCABB", 
        "correct": "CBBCABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCABCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8129055767145558, 
        "stimulus": 1574, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAACB", 
        "correct": "CAAACBC", 
        "incorrect": "CAAACCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1562562938037566, 
        "stimulus": 1560, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAC", 
        "correct": "BCACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.134871155829049, 
        "stimulus": 1069, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACC", 
        "correct": "CACCC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1601786766701139, 
        "stimulus": 1223, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBCBB", 
        "correct": "ACBBCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBBCBCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2738252566382053, 
        "stimulus": 1780, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACAB", 
        "correct": "AACABC", 
        "incorrect": "AACACB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0606166518038471, 
        "stimulus": 1566, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCAC", 
        "correct": "ABCACC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9009928828867181, 
        "stimulus": 1368, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCCBACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCCBACB", 
        "correct": "ABBCCBACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCCBACCB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3682863054834258, 
        "stimulus": 1889, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACA", 
        "correct": "AACAC", 
        "incorrect": "AACCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.051468172656947, 
        "stimulus": 1034, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACACBACBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACACBACBBA", 
        "correct": "ACACBACBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACACBACBBCA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5529785300956431, 
        "stimulus": 1104, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCACBCBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCACBCBBB", 
        "correct": "CBCACBCBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCACBCBBCB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3815818295085618, 
        "stimulus": 1800, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABACACCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACACCCC", 
        "correct": "ABACACCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "ABACCACCCC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4585667939477263, 
        "stimulus": 1841, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBCACBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCACBAB", 
        "correct": "CBBCACBABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCACBACB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2357702315555839, 
        "stimulus": 1503, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCCB", 
        "correct": "ACBCCBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBCCCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1809394991789677, 
        "stimulus": 1185, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCBC", 
        "correct": "BCCBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9009928828867181, 
        "stimulus": 1700, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBAACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBAACB", 
        "correct": "ACBBAACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBBAACCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4081278034618925, 
        "stimulus": 1435, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAABACABAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAABACABAC", 
        "correct": "AAABACABACC", 
        "incorrect": "AAABACABCAC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.358435091172191, 
        "stimulus": 1767, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACA", 
        "correct": "ACAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0661695771284148, 
        "stimulus": 1236, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBABBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBABBBC", 
        "correct": "ACBABBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBABBCBC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2799255046912512, 
        "stimulus": 1601, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAAA", 
        "correct": "CACAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CACAACA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8779157647474438, 
        "stimulus": 1281, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAB", 
        "correct": "ABABC", 
        "incorrect": "ABACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2570787221094177, 
        "stimulus": 1307, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBA", 
        "correct": "ACBAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.09450722608594, 
        "stimulus": 1031, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCAC", 
        "correct": "CCCACC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8347065795168704, 
        "stimulus": 1399, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCAB", 
        "correct": "CBBCABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCACB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1504834564483348, 
        "stimulus": 1274, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAB", 
        "correct": "BCABC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.09450722608594, 
        "stimulus": 1319, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABCABCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCABCA", 
        "correct": "BABCABCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BABCABCCA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3672814722654612, 
        "stimulus": 1376, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACABAAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACABAAAC", 
        "correct": "CACABAAACC", 
        "incorrect": "CACABAACAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4357973040398446, 
        "stimulus": 1907, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAAAACCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAAAACCB", 
        "correct": "CBAAAACCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAAAACCCB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2043334457988326, 
        "stimulus": 1254, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCA", 
        "correct": "ABCAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2621441266152613, 
        "stimulus": 1249, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABACBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABACBAC", 
        "correct": "BABACBACC", 
        "incorrect": "BABACBCAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3029288428872636, 
        "stimulus": 1326, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCACABCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACABCBA", 
        "correct": "CCACABCBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACABCBCA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.6366744872217038, 
        "stimulus": 1381, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBA", 
        "correct": "CBCBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9669926703678359, 
        "stimulus": 1552, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCABACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABACA", 
        "correct": "BCABACAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCABACCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.2981423969999719, 
        "stimulus": 1481, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBCBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCBBA", 
        "correct": "BCBCBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCBBCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1488675577884433, 
        "stimulus": 1513, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBABA", 
        "correct": "BCBABAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBABCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.348892587945653, 
        "stimulus": 1207, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCABAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABAA", 
        "correct": "BCABAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCABACA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2507666837607143, 
        "stimulus": 1214, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCBCACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCBCACAA", 
        "correct": "CABCBCACAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCBCACACA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4764596166841708, 
        "stimulus": 1807, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBABAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBABAA", 
        "correct": "BBABAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBABACA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0043907571402493, 
        "stimulus": 1642, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCCABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCCABA", 
        "correct": "CABCCABAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCCABCA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5033679699209443, 
        "stimulus": 1590, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCCA", 
        "correct": "CBBCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCCCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1023727583032077, 
        "stimulus": 1094, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBBCCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBBCCBA", 
        "correct": "BBBBCCBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBBBCCBCA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0555280348500893, 
        "stimulus": 1963, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBB", 
        "correct": "ABBBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.092011574037053, 
        "stimulus": 1046, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBA", 
        "correct": "BBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBBCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.052998134469838, 
        "stimulus": 1142, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACBBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACBBBB", 
        "correct": "BACBBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BACBBBCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.187138345398739, 
        "stimulus": 1883, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCABA", 
        "correct": "BCCABAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCABCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9052296279413065, 
        "stimulus": 1457, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBC", 
        "correct": "CBBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3168818732052172, 
        "stimulus": 1719, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACCCC", 
        "correct": "CBACCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCACCCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1031282354412366, 
        "stimulus": 1843, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCABCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCABCB", 
        "correct": "BBCABCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCABCCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2951711616865997, 
        "stimulus": 1709, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACB", 
        "correct": "BCACBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2746910464346828, 
        "stimulus": 1945, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAABAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAABAAC", 
        "correct": "BAABAACC", 
        "incorrect": "BAABACAC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3776018683157731, 
        "stimulus": 1980, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAAAA", 
        "correct": "CAAAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CAAAACA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.026663725878403, 
        "stimulus": 1973, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBBAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBBAAA", 
        "correct": "ABBBAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBAACA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.287705843741087, 
        "stimulus": 1664, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAABBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAABBBA", 
        "correct": "CAABBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CAABBBCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3360840402937344, 
        "stimulus": 1441, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACCAC", 
        "correct": "CBACCACC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACCCAC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1541571584771664, 
        "stimulus": 1369, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAA", 
        "correct": "CCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.132464458695859, 
        "stimulus": 1106, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCCC", 
        "correct": "BABCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BACBCCC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4634102677052347, 
        "stimulus": 1937, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCABACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCABACB", 
        "correct": "ACCABACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACCABACCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4214898970331777, 
        "stimulus": 1302, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAA", 
        "correct": "CBAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.001285467032941, 
        "stimulus": 1361, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAAA", 
        "correct": "ACAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACAACA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9479967741538518, 
        "stimulus": 1882, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACA", 
        "correct": "CBACAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBACCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0594948478020583, 
        "stimulus": 1125, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABCCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABCCBB", 
        "correct": "CBABCCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBABCCBCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9680553009922933, 
        "stimulus": 1433, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBCBBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBCBBBC", 
        "correct": "BBBCBBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BBBCBBCBC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0135836553547783, 
        "stimulus": 1824, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACCC", 
        "correct": "BACCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCACCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2437113275185634, 
        "stimulus": 1215, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCC", 
        "correct": "CBCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0468434593895515, 
        "stimulus": 1792, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBACBCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBACBCCA", 
        "correct": "ACBBACBCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBBACBCCCA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5332106659468336, 
        "stimulus": 1812, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAABCACBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAABCACBC", 
        "correct": "AAABCACBCC", 
        "incorrect": "AAABCACCBC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3331493708448097, 
        "stimulus": 1285, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAAA", 
        "correct": "ABAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABAACA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1498666856329771, 
        "stimulus": 1250, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACCAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACCAAA", 
        "correct": "AACCAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "AACCAACA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.49182987703022196, 
        "stimulus": 1075, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCBAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBAAC", 
        "correct": "ABCBAACC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBACAC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.159669645641575, 
        "stimulus": 1775, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCABBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABBB", 
        "correct": "BCABBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCABBCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3045451925360043, 
        "stimulus": 1195, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBB", 
        "correct": "ABCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.6821510941214326, 
        "stimulus": 1723, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBA", 
        "correct": "ABBAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3308708081915064, 
        "stimulus": 1313, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABBBB", 
        "correct": "BABBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BABBBCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8467711080428172, 
        "stimulus": 1341, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCAA", 
        "correct": "CABCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCACA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1130563046415383, 
        "stimulus": 1826, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCA", 
        "correct": "CCBCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.9951371400768987, 
        "stimulus": 1235, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAAB", 
        "correct": "BAABC", 
        "incorrect": "BAACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.119702400755972, 
        "stimulus": 1241, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBBC", 
        "correct": "CABBBCC", 
        "incorrect": "CABBCBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1568512469553562, 
        "stimulus": 1970, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBBCCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBBCCAA", 
        "correct": "BBCBBCCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCBBCCACA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4121841424604722, 
        "stimulus": 1335, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAABAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAABAB", 
        "correct": "ACAABABC", 
        "incorrect": "ACAABACB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.7352937555119898, 
        "stimulus": 1017, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAAAB", 
        "correct": "AAAABC", 
        "incorrect": "AAAACB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0606166518038471, 
        "stimulus": 1263, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAACBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAACBB", 
        "correct": "CBAACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAACBCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.0267821818853078, 
        "stimulus": 1206, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBA", 
        "correct": "CBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8984041307564036, 
        "stimulus": 1026, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACABAABBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACABAABBBB", 
        "correct": "ACABAABBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACABAABBBCB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.4263405596990366, 
        "stimulus": 1183, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBCBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCBCB", 
        "correct": "CCBCBCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCBCCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8381656327597566, 
        "stimulus": 1975, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACA", 
        "correct": "ABACAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABACCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3711987230628533, 
        "stimulus": 1473, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBAC", 
        "correct": "CCCBACC", 
        "incorrect": "CCCBCAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.1795464878134951, 
        "stimulus": 1915, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAACBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACBB", 
        "correct": "CAACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CAACBCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 0.8353563919241512, 
        "stimulus": 1886, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBBABAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBABAC", 
        "correct": "CCBBABACC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBBABCAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5151204719356475, 
        "stimulus": 1845, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABCABCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCABCCC", 
        "correct": "BABCABCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BABCACBCCC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.5178075212893753, 
        "stimulus": 1948, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCACCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCACCB", 
        "correct": "BCCACCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCACCCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2951711616865997, 
        "stimulus": 1553, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCBBBBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCBBBBCC", 
        "correct": "ABBCBBBBCCC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCBBBCBCC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.3020043008996856, 
        "stimulus": 1840, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCB", 
        "correct": "BCBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": ">=C>", 
        "score": 1.2121830534626528, 
        "stimulus": 1255, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCC", 
        "correct": "BCC", 
        "incorrect": "BAC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7382707643286959, 
        "stimulus": 2270, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAAC", 
        "correct": "BAB", 
        "incorrect": "BBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9802826510675678, 
        "stimulus": 2159, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCACA", 
        "correct": "ACCCBA", 
        "incorrect": "ACCCBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.608059649451369, 
        "stimulus": 2168, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AC", 
        "correct": "B", 
        "incorrect": "A", 
        "length": 2, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.640278333181836, 
        "stimulus": 1995, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAAC", 
        "correct": "BCAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9222889394647223, 
        "stimulus": 2204, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAC", 
        "correct": "CB", 
        "incorrect": "AB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9393263883192159, 
        "stimulus": 1999, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBB", 
        "correct": "BBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8159107253932402, 
        "stimulus": 2244, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACCA", 
        "correct": "ABBCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6816064319711607, 
        "stimulus": 2950, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABAAACCBB", 
        "correct": "AABAABCBB", 
        "incorrect": "AABABCCBB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5650248986925566, 
        "stimulus": 2096, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAC", 
        "correct": "BB", 
        "incorrect": "AB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.2765240854622648, 
        "stimulus": 2016, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBACB", 
        "correct": "BBBACB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBACB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.03589889550646, 
        "stimulus": 2101, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACC", 
        "correct": "BC", 
        "incorrect": "BA", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7554942785609111, 
        "stimulus": 2003, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBCCBBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCBBCCBBA", 
        "correct": "CBCBBCCBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CABBBCCBBA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0461262217379577, 
        "stimulus": 2240, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABAAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBABAAB", 
        "correct": "CBBABAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBABAAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0997382852348807, 
        "stimulus": 2887, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACACACAC", 
        "correct": "AACBACAC", 
        "incorrect": "AACABCAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6626283287667717, 
        "stimulus": 2669, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACA", 
        "correct": "BA", 
        "incorrect": "BC", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4919766495072682, 
        "stimulus": 2058, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACB", 
        "correct": "ABB", 
        "incorrect": "BAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7224860063348436, 
        "stimulus": 2012, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACC", 
        "correct": "BBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7026778451511226, 
        "stimulus": 2053, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAAAACCAB", 
        "correct": "CCAAABCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CCAABCCAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8615430248519744, 
        "stimulus": 2878, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACACAAAB", 
        "correct": "CCACBAAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CCABCAAAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7007442844341637, 
        "stimulus": 2480, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAC", 
        "correct": "ACB", 
        "incorrect": "AAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9901995251687694, 
        "stimulus": 2133, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACCBCCA", 
        "correct": "BBCBCCA", 
        "incorrect": "BABBCCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.794308436926819, 
        "stimulus": 2760, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCAAA", 
        "correct": "BCAAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABAAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5571366742517332, 
        "stimulus": 2815, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACAABA", 
        "correct": "ABAABA", 
        "incorrect": "AABABA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7404288926541467, 
        "stimulus": 2728, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABACACCBA", 
        "correct": "CABACBCBA", 
        "incorrect": "CABABCCBA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9331440103034045, 
        "stimulus": 2692, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAACBCBB", 
        "correct": "CCABBCBB", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCBCBB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6365937936849458, 
        "stimulus": 2644, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAC", 
        "correct": "AB", 
        "incorrect": "BA", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7554942785609111, 
        "stimulus": 2031, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBAC", 
        "correct": "BBB", 
        "incorrect": "BAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.03059582412587, 
        "stimulus": 2022, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBA", 
        "correct": "BBBA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8660964696990588, 
        "stimulus": 2466, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAC", 
        "correct": "CCB", 
        "incorrect": "CAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6936627122535747, 
        "stimulus": 2165, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACB", 
        "correct": "CBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6487005107351542, 
        "stimulus": 2079, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACCAAAA", 
        "correct": "ABBCAAAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABABAAAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5783264416915819, 
        "stimulus": 2671, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAAA", 
        "correct": "BAAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5653095723144269, 
        "stimulus": 2403, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACBCBB", 
        "correct": "ABBBCBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABABCBB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6677729119425513, 
        "stimulus": 2499, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAA", 
        "correct": "BAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8333280918825671, 
        "stimulus": 2174, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBACA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCACBBACA", 
        "correct": "CBCBBBACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCBBACA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0080224287163426, 
        "stimulus": 2839, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACACCB", 
        "correct": "CBBACCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBABCCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7722058148754519, 
        "stimulus": 2390, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCCBAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCBAABACB", 
        "correct": "ACCCBAABBB", 
        "incorrect": "ACCCBAABCB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.2554441631716111, 
        "stimulus": 2417, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAACAAACC", 
        "correct": "BCAACAABC", 
        "incorrect": "BCAACAABA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9472102124131052, 
        "stimulus": 2838, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBAACB", 
        "correct": "BBBABB", 
        "incorrect": "BBBBAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7359123878681648, 
        "stimulus": 2406, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCAC", 
        "correct": "BABCB", 
        "incorrect": "BABCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7914647913187668, 
        "stimulus": 2665, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACC", 
        "correct": "CBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4275585688333779, 
        "stimulus": 2042, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAAAC", 
        "correct": "CCAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CCAAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9081171418910816, 
        "stimulus": 2627, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABAC", 
        "correct": "CABB", 
        "incorrect": "CABC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0612599832541003, 
        "stimulus": 2312, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCA", 
        "correct": "BCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6318163851533961, 
        "stimulus": 2093, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABACCA", 
        "correct": "BABBCA", 
        "incorrect": "BABCBA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.3879397520008959, 
        "stimulus": 2020, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAACBBC", 
        "correct": "BABBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCBBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6787339050918964, 
        "stimulus": 2759, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACA", 
        "correct": "CCBA", 
        "incorrect": "CCBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.3532594906478224, 
        "stimulus": 2136, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACBBCAC", 
        "correct": "BCBBBCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCBBCAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8132660449964559, 
        "stimulus": 2726, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAACA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACACBAACA", 
        "correct": "CAACBBAACA", 
        "incorrect": "CAABCBAACA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.747732067253048, 
        "stimulus": 2318, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCBA", 
        "correct": "BCBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.334488738299786, 
        "stimulus": 2127, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCBBB", 
        "correct": "CBCBBB", 
        "incorrect": "CABBBB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8265981790331588, 
        "stimulus": 2630, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACAC", 
        "correct": "ABAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6860577908777926, 
        "stimulus": 2689, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACA", 
        "correct": "CBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6686423772090002, 
        "stimulus": 2227, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCAC", 
        "correct": "CBCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.779183856632804, 
        "stimulus": 2864, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCB", 
        "correct": "BCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.838668420655936, 
        "stimulus": 2007, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACACCA", 
        "correct": "ABACBCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABABCCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7820170892485566, 
        "stimulus": 2743, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCABCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCABCC", 
        "correct": "BBCABCC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCABCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0182925358852146, 
        "stimulus": 2666, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACACB", 
        "correct": "BBACB", 
        "incorrect": "BABCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6873605725983488, 
        "stimulus": 2341, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCCCCC", 
        "correct": "CBCCCCC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCCCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9504934545196659, 
        "stimulus": 2206, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAAAAAC", 
        "correct": "BAAAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BAAAAA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.2884236125787136, 
        "stimulus": 2899, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABAC", 
        "correct": "BABB", 
        "incorrect": "BABC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.513535627256631, 
        "stimulus": 2484, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACACCBAA", 
        "correct": "ACBCBAA", 
        "incorrect": "ACABBAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7374488603832297, 
        "stimulus": 2717, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBAB", 
        "correct": "CBBAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7441598090227354, 
        "stimulus": 2363, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACACCA", 
        "correct": "ACBCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6096020919181067, 
        "stimulus": 2992, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAB", 
        "correct": "BAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.844704712967158, 
        "stimulus": 2173, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCAACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCAACAACC", 
        "correct": "BCCAACABC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCAACABA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.101077189703752, 
        "stimulus": 2246, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        11, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACBBACCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACBBACCCAC", 
        "correct": "AACBBACCCB", 
        "incorrect": "AACBBACCCC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.4074452236654127, 
        "stimulus": 2077, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACBABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACBABAAC", 
        "correct": "CBACBABAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBACBABAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.5145492198352501, 
        "stimulus": 2542, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAC", 
        "correct": "BAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7382707643286959, 
        "stimulus": 2010, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACBAC", 
        "correct": "ABBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BABAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5242232594838847, 
        "stimulus": 2783, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBCAAC", 
        "correct": "CCCBCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CCCBCAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9459731220836339, 
        "stimulus": 2340, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAACCBBC", 
        "correct": "CBABCBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAABBBC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7021043323799532, 
        "stimulus": 2388, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACACA", 
        "correct": "BCACBA", 
        "incorrect": "BCACBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7422847632919597, 
        "stimulus": 2235, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABAC", 
        "correct": "AABB", 
        "incorrect": "ABAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9985824458502812, 
        "stimulus": 2085, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBACCCABB", 
        "correct": "CBBBCCABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBABCABB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8986095389937329, 
        "stimulus": 2078, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACBABA", 
        "correct": "ABBABA", 
        "incorrect": "BABABA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6013630828288057, 
        "stimulus": 2483, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAAAC", 
        "correct": "CBAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABAAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8148643235229796, 
        "stimulus": 2063, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBABAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBABABACB", 
        "correct": "BBABABBB", 
        "incorrect": "BBABABCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8050162175584163, 
        "stimulus": 1997, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACABBA", 
        "correct": "BABBA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.2571297386132901, 
        "stimulus": 2602, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCAACBBC", 
        "correct": "CBCABBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBCBBC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7758441816180336, 
        "stimulus": 2420, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBACA", 
        "correct": "CBBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6713143863423796, 
        "stimulus": 2543, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCBBAC", 
        "correct": "BCBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8601116949184677, 
        "stimulus": 2203, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACB", 
        "correct": "BB", 
        "incorrect": "BC", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.885908609165089, 
        "stimulus": 2023, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAABB", 
        "correct": "BAABB", 
        "incorrect": "BCABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.866082381613216, 
        "stimulus": 2672, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBBACABAA", 
        "correct": "BBBBBABAA", 
        "incorrect": "BBBBABBAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8777418605430097, 
        "stimulus": 2603, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBACBBAAC", 
        "correct": "BCBBBBAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBABBAAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8471022049230472, 
        "stimulus": 2865, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBBACBBA", 
        "correct": "CBBBBBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBCBBA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8961395634541125, 
        "stimulus": 2494, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBAC", 
        "correct": "BCBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8037605978717756, 
        "stimulus": 2247, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAABACCAA", 
        "correct": "CBAABBCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBAABABAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5472016065749629, 
        "stimulus": 2886, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBABACBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCBABACBB", 
        "correct": "BBCBABACBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBABACBB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.2546247550740621, 
        "stimulus": 2186, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACCB", 
        "correct": "ABBCB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7508401173508678, 
        "stimulus": 2220, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACACB", 
        "correct": "CACBB", 
        "incorrect": "CABCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5913545727195069, 
        "stimulus": 2571, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCACCAA", 
        "correct": "ACCBCAA", 
        "incorrect": "ACBCCAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6281020298248324, 
        "stimulus": 2929, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAACB", 
        "correct": "CAABB", 
        "incorrect": "CACBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.817775721817953, 
        "stimulus": 2338, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACBACC", 
        "correct": "BACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BACBCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.916465256501912, 
        "stimulus": 2767, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACCCBC", 
        "correct": "CCBCCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CCABCBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7288962569658438, 
        "stimulus": 2934, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBBAC", 
        "correct": "ABCBBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.815774603910515, 
        "stimulus": 2592, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBACBACBAB", 
        "correct": "BBACBBBAB", 
        "incorrect": "BBACBCBAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6884346482455381, 
        "stimulus": 2816, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCA", 
        "correct": "BCCA", 
        "incorrect": "BACA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4642238909693713, 
        "stimulus": 2176, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAACCABB", 
        "correct": "BABCABB", 
        "incorrect": "BAABABB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8351004288218519, 
        "stimulus": 2377, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABACCCC", 
        "correct": "BCABBCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BCABABCC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8524167208648994, 
        "stimulus": 2451, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAACA", 
        "correct": "AABA", 
        "incorrect": "AABC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7119994935427189, 
        "stimulus": 2396, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABBAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCABBAA", 
        "correct": "BCABBAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABABBAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.125149006546871, 
        "stimulus": 2449, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAABAC", 
        "correct": "AAABB", 
        "incorrect": "AAABC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.877650764653727, 
        "stimulus": 2275, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCACCABCC", 
        "correct": "CCCBCABCC", 
        "incorrect": "CCCABABCC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7080652831544508, 
        "stimulus": 2874, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACABA", 
        "correct": "BABA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.31426968052735443, 
        "stimulus": 2439, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCBBCB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACABCBBCB", 
        "correct": "BABCBBCB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCBBCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8968881497810303, 
        "stimulus": 2621, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBBABC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCBBABC", 
        "correct": "BCCBBABC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBBABC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.1874461199274893, 
        "stimulus": 2392, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAACCAA", 
        "correct": "CACABCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CACBCCAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7789416873490379, 
        "stimulus": 2971, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAC", 
        "correct": "CBAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9381073682102885, 
        "stimulus": 2300, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACCCAAB", 
        "correct": "ABCCAAB", 
        "incorrect": "AABCAAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9005333048826923, 
        "stimulus": 2161, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACC", 
        "correct": "CCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5653095723144269, 
        "stimulus": 2694, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACAC", 
        "correct": "BACB", 
        "incorrect": "BACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0652098764444626, 
        "stimulus": 2385, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBACA", 
        "correct": "CABBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CABBBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7805281809210016, 
        "stimulus": 2957, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCAC", 
        "correct": "BCCB", 
        "incorrect": "BCAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9449575011280177, 
        "stimulus": 2205, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACA", 
        "correct": "ABBA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7501022069780999, 
        "stimulus": 2099, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACCCBC", 
        "correct": "ABCCBC", 
        "incorrect": "AABCBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7016011780273816, 
        "stimulus": 2370, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCACAA", 
        "correct": "BCCBAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCAA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7041383383542926, 
        "stimulus": 2201, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAABAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCAABAC", 
        "correct": "BBCAABAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCAABAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.1574145088702015, 
        "stimulus": 2135, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABACA", 
        "correct": "AABBA", 
        "incorrect": "AABBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5242232594838847, 
        "stimulus": 2519, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACA", 
        "correct": "CBA", 
        "incorrect": "ABA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8940961322556751, 
        "stimulus": 2074, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBBBCACA", 
        "correct": "ABBBBCBA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBBBCA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.906970314709309, 
        "stimulus": 1998, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCAABACB", 
        "correct": "ACCAABBB", 
        "incorrect": "ACCAABCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0189336644063838, 
        "stimulus": 2356, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBAB", 
        "correct": "BBAB", 
        "incorrect": "BABB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6426777459538128, 
        "stimulus": 2506, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACAA", 
        "correct": "ABAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8928990837925181, 
        "stimulus": 2460, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBACACB", 
        "correct": "BBBACB", 
        "incorrect": "BBABCB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6787339050918964, 
        "stimulus": 2722, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCACA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACCCCACA", 
        "correct": "ABCCCACA", 
        "incorrect": "AABCCACA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8383348076975722, 
        "stimulus": 2564, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAACCA", 
        "correct": "BAACCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABACCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9157822819849765, 
        "stimulus": 2090, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCAACAC", 
        "correct": "ACCABAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACCBCAC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7341542511354866, 
        "stimulus": 2158, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAC", 
        "correct": "CBB", 
        "incorrect": "BAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8576695986571886, 
        "stimulus": 2064, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACC", 
        "correct": "CABC", 
        "incorrect": "CABA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4875331034134381, 
        "stimulus": 2033, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBBCBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACCBBBCBC", 
        "correct": "ABCBBBCBC", 
        "incorrect": "AABBBBCBC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8395854528874984, 
        "stimulus": 2348, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBACCBBAA", 
        "correct": "ABCBBCBBAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBABBBAA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.904362226418327, 
        "stimulus": 2153, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCAA", 
        "correct": "CBCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CABAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7198287787016656, 
        "stimulus": 2043, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAABACC", 
        "correct": "CBAABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBAABCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0743447685057355, 
        "stimulus": 2545, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACAAC", 
        "correct": "CCBAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCAAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6763884898896371, 
        "stimulus": 2561, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBACACCBB", 
        "correct": "ACBBBACCBB", 
        "incorrect": "ACBBABCCBB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6608756275885516, 
        "stimulus": 2241, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBA", 
        "correct": "BBA", 
        "incorrect": "BAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6727516052199968, 
        "stimulus": 2068, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABBABCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBABBABCC", 
        "correct": "BBABBABCC", 
        "incorrect": "ABABBABCC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9277976777793212, 
        "stimulus": 2901, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBCAC", 
        "correct": "BBBCAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5657054146632023, 
        "stimulus": 2265, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABCACBBA", 
        "correct": "AABCBBBA", 
        "incorrect": "AABBCBBA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8255892030078443, 
        "stimulus": 2825, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCACCAA", 
        "correct": "CBCBCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7888170242854422, 
        "stimulus": 2554, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACC", 
        "correct": "ABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0476710993946785, 
        "stimulus": 2075, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACCAC", 
        "correct": "ABCAC", 
        "incorrect": "AABAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7887744642837992, 
        "stimulus": 2446, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAABAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBAABAC", 
        "correct": "BBBAABAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBAABAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.972144402896977, 
        "stimulus": 2330, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBAABBACBAB", 
        "correct": "BBAABBBBAB", 
        "incorrect": "BBAABBCBAB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7790046274291895, 
        "stimulus": 2411, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABBAAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAABBAAC", 
        "correct": "CBAABBAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABABBAAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0574871272629116, 
        "stimulus": 2148, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCCB", 
        "correct": "CBCCB", 
        "incorrect": "CABCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7292346675044805, 
        "stimulus": 2179, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBAC", 
        "correct": "CBBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0930223078043104, 
        "stimulus": 2172, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBACCBCC", 
        "correct": "BBBBCBCC", 
        "incorrect": "BBBABBCC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8504221136565481, 
        "stimulus": 2402, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBACACC", 
        "correct": "ACBBACC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBABCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.83821154520771, 
        "stimulus": 2657, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCAAC", 
        "correct": "CBCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8258843282531687, 
        "stimulus": 2476, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACA", 
        "correct": "ABA", 
        "incorrect": "CBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0476710993946785, 
        "stimulus": 2181, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACCCBCA", 
        "correct": "CABCCBCA", 
        "incorrect": "CAABCBCA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7482791795837122, 
        "stimulus": 2840, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBBAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCBBBAB", 
        "correct": "BCBBBAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBBAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4614823627801801, 
        "stimulus": 2195, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABAC", 
        "correct": "CBABB", 
        "incorrect": "CBABC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8408897006577706, 
        "stimulus": 2628, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAA", 
        "correct": "CBAA", 
        "incorrect": "BAAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8143855449592555, 
        "stimulus": 2397, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBAC", 
        "correct": "ABBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5339988537968516, 
        "stimulus": 2750, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBCB", 
        "correct": "BBBCB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5604914729893506, 
        "stimulus": 2893, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACACC", 
        "correct": "BCBACC", 
        "incorrect": "BCABCC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4932487831947412, 
        "stimulus": 2164, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACACA", 
        "correct": "BACA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8625921326889399, 
        "stimulus": 2798, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBACBBB", 
        "correct": "ACBBBBBB", 
        "incorrect": "ACBBCBBB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.678186573492753, 
        "stimulus": 2660, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAACB", 
        "correct": "CBAACB", 
        "incorrect": "CABACB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7665057048596389, 
        "stimulus": 2596, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACBABA", 
        "correct": "CABBABA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBABA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5988761168632425, 
        "stimulus": 2317, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAACCCBB", 
        "correct": "ACABCCBB", 
        "incorrect": "ACBCCCBB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8252309954559532, 
        "stimulus": 2432, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACAACC", 
        "correct": "ABAACC", 
        "incorrect": "AABACC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.791838895949756, 
        "stimulus": 2744, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACBA", 
        "correct": "BBBA", 
        "incorrect": "BBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8629853121942025, 
        "stimulus": 2251, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBACAB", 
        "correct": "BBBAB", 
        "incorrect": "BBABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5042131723247408, 
        "stimulus": 2073, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAAC", 
        "correct": "AAB", 
        "incorrect": "ACB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9166719618461189, 
        "stimulus": 2070, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAAB", 
        "correct": "BAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8940948321385842, 
        "stimulus": 2122, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACA", 
        "correct": "BBA", 
        "incorrect": "BBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8931342395528289, 
        "stimulus": 2126, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCCACC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCCCACC", 
        "correct": "BCCCCACC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCCACC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9253497650012236, 
        "stimulus": 2305, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCACB", 
        "correct": "ABCBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.793647644929917, 
        "stimulus": 2880, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBACBAC", 
        "correct": "BBBBAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBBABC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6486298271137415, 
        "stimulus": 2735, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBC", 
        "correct": "BBC", 
        "incorrect": "BAC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0303976815319937, 
        "stimulus": 2081, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAC", 
        "correct": "ABB", 
        "incorrect": "BAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8462009907819688, 
        "stimulus": 2209, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACBBBA", 
        "correct": "CABBBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6946979596349336, 
        "stimulus": 2585, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        11, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCAACABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCAACABAAC", 
        "correct": "ACCAACABAB", 
        "incorrect": "ACCAACABAA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.2775028819974024, 
        "stimulus": 2529, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBACB", 
        "correct": "CBBB", 
        "incorrect": "BBAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8228739578439201, 
        "stimulus": 2116, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCC", 
        "correct": "BCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8210006329039615, 
        "stimulus": 2046, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAC", 
        "correct": "BCB", 
        "incorrect": "BAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9802826510675678, 
        "stimulus": 2004, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCAACC", 
        "correct": "CCABC", 
        "incorrect": "CCABA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7495689095576933, 
        "stimulus": 2673, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBACC", 
        "correct": "BBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BBBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8070052172748172, 
        "stimulus": 2777, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCAAC", 
        "correct": "BCCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCAAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.517752848336968, 
        "stimulus": 2198, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACACC", 
        "correct": "AACBC", 
        "incorrect": "AACBA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8043258439944917, 
        "stimulus": 1996, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCCACCBC", 
        "correct": "CACCCBCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CACCBCCBC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.763935692846113, 
        "stimulus": 2544, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACC", 
        "correct": "ABBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.542885454962382, 
        "stimulus": 2589, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACACBA", 
        "correct": "BBACBA", 
        "incorrect": "BAACBA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.697879195988252, 
        "stimulus": 2512, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABACC", 
        "correct": "CABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4880948175516282, 
        "stimulus": 2683, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBCACB", 
        "correct": "CBBCACB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCACB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8158189672684316, 
        "stimulus": 2367, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACACC", 
        "correct": "ACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5164731179350591, 
        "stimulus": 2149, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAACBCC", 
        "correct": "ABABBCC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCBCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6139675743911184, 
        "stimulus": 2028, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAACCBCAC", 
        "correct": "AABCBCAC", 
        "incorrect": "AAABBCAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8254546446346878, 
        "stimulus": 2707, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABACACAB", 
        "correct": "ABBACAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABABCAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7488299306063462, 
        "stimulus": 2916, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCAAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCAAAAAC", 
        "correct": "CCCAAAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CCCAAAAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.3870675012380334, 
        "stimulus": 2737, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAAAC", 
        "correct": "BAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BAAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8816881459021633, 
        "stimulus": 2167, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAACA", 
        "correct": "CBABA", 
        "incorrect": "CBABC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.616657436323532, 
        "stimulus": 2169, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCBBBA", 
        "correct": "BCBBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBBA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8123089157342985, 
        "stimulus": 2120, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACACABB", 
        "correct": "ACBABB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCABB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4872279459165862, 
        "stimulus": 2283, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAACCA", 
        "correct": "BABCA", 
        "incorrect": "BBCCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5940237490612512, 
        "stimulus": 2818, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBACACCB", 
        "correct": "BCBACBCB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBABCCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8169578432384819, 
        "stimulus": 2152, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCACB", 
        "correct": "CBCBB", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6866775440790336, 
        "stimulus": 2207, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACB", 
        "correct": "BBB", 
        "incorrect": "BBC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6585766130285139, 
        "stimulus": 2067, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACBC", 
        "correct": "ABBC", 
        "incorrect": "BABC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7758058421147602, 
        "stimulus": 2139, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBAAC", 
        "correct": "CCBAB", 
        "incorrect": "CCBAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6334094185839981, 
        "stimulus": 2117, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBAACAB", 
        "correct": "ABBABAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBCAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8217237978030729, 
        "stimulus": 2197, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCAACBACB", 
        "correct": "ABCCABBACB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCBCBACB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7299926842533865, 
        "stimulus": 2593, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCAC", 
        "correct": "BBCB", 
        "incorrect": "BBAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9840856757466356, 
        "stimulus": 2525, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCBBAC", 
        "correct": "BCBCBBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCBBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.1503974558212944, 
        "stimulus": 2828, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCBBA", 
        "correct": "CBCBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CABBBA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8375742265053622, 
        "stimulus": 2526, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAAACB", 
        "correct": "AAABB", 
        "incorrect": "AACBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9754387362526531, 
        "stimulus": 2659, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACACBC", 
        "correct": "CCACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACCBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8585067965621712, 
        "stimulus": 2607, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAACA", 
        "correct": "CABA", 
        "incorrect": "CABC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4600537971526872, 
        "stimulus": 2344, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACA", 
        "correct": "BCBA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7510829788521831, 
        "stimulus": 2568, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAACB", 
        "correct": "ACABB", 
        "incorrect": "ACBCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8081311549819659, 
        "stimulus": 2257, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCB", 
        "correct": "CBCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.4978452161338349, 
        "stimulus": 2454, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCCABAA", 
        "correct": "BCCABAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCABAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.0013945071833872, 
        "stimulus": 2606, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBBACA", 
        "correct": "CBCBBBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.726708341789939, 
        "stimulus": 2847, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBBC", 
        "correct": "CBBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5417792268797293, 
        "stimulus": 2351, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCACCAC", 
        "correct": "CCCBCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCCAC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5521301257012181, 
        "stimulus": 2601, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBACACA", 
        "correct": "CBBACBA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBACBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6300750534164261, 
        "stimulus": 2952, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAAC", 
        "correct": "CBAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9449295197056092, 
        "stimulus": 2250, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBAACBAAA", 
        "correct": "CBABBAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCBAAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8161888108449808, 
        "stimulus": 2846, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBACBA", 
        "correct": "BBBBBA", 
        "incorrect": "BBBCBA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6592067209742971, 
        "stimulus": 2523, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAABC", 
        "correct": "BAABC", 
        "incorrect": "BCABC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.685196756897815, 
        "stimulus": 2509, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBACBB", 
        "correct": "BBBBB", 
        "incorrect": "BBCAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.46365627093221096, 
        "stimulus": 2104, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACAB", 
        "correct": "ABAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6860577908777926, 
        "stimulus": 2522, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCACA", 
        "correct": "ACCBA", 
        "incorrect": "ACCBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8558734998983507, 
        "stimulus": 2540, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBAAACA", 
        "correct": "BBAABA", 
        "incorrect": "BBAABC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7912633708141128, 
        "stimulus": 2441, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAACB", 
        "correct": "BAACB", 
        "incorrect": "BCACB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5266340499403854, 
        "stimulus": 2394, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAACCBCC", 
        "correct": "AABCBCC", 
        "incorrect": "AAABBCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8249172038578783, 
        "stimulus": 2793, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAACCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAACCAACBB", 
        "correct": "ABAACCABBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABAACCBCBB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.9390142143131719, 
        "stimulus": 2236, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBAABBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBAABBCAC", 
        "correct": "BCBAABBCB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBAABBCC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.4001260217592666, 
        "stimulus": 2128, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBACB", 
        "correct": "BBACB", 
        "incorrect": "ABACB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7285159175842512, 
        "stimulus": 2912, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCAACA", 
        "correct": "CABCABA", 
        "incorrect": "CABCABC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.3607992880685279, 
        "stimulus": 2655, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBBCCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCBBBCCC", 
        "correct": "BCBBBCCC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBBCCC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8946975971421219, 
        "stimulus": 2616, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCBC", 
        "correct": "BCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6677040639423062, 
        "stimulus": 2170, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABABACAC", 
        "correct": "AABABBAC", 
        "incorrect": "AABABCAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8451130927880539, 
        "stimulus": 2259, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBBAC", 
        "correct": "BBBBB", 
        "incorrect": "BBBBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 1.1560348461823944, 
        "stimulus": 2915, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABAAC", 
        "correct": "AABAB", 
        "incorrect": "AABAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.43451955449032503, 
        "stimulus": 2938, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBB", 
        "correct": "CBBB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8259922502400528, 
        "stimulus": 2940, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCA", 
        "correct": "CBCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.44549651309293326, 
        "stimulus": 2968, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABBBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAABBBA", 
        "correct": "BAABBBA", 
        "incorrect": "AAABBBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8270356567950233, 
        "stimulus": 2913, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACBBC", 
        "correct": "BBBBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.7963946090346472, 
        "stimulus": 2124, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCACB", 
        "correct": "CCCBB", 
        "incorrect": "CCABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5697082592753966, 
        "stimulus": 2321, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAACABC", 
        "correct": "ABABABC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCABC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8044147378855393, 
        "stimulus": 2877, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACBCA", 
        "correct": "ABBCA", 
        "incorrect": "BABCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8248154046226585, 
        "stimulus": 2565, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCACCC", 
        "correct": "CBBCBCC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBBCCC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5646896245609597, 
        "stimulus": 2772, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCABCA", 
        "correct": "CBCABCA", 
        "incorrect": "CABABCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.5999755312708572, 
        "stimulus": 2333, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBAC", 
        "correct": "BBBB", 
        "incorrect": "BBBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.513535627256631, 
        "stimulus": 2145, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACAAC", 
        "correct": "CACAB", 
        "incorrect": "CACAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.955766646379687, 
        "stimulus": 2014, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACCACC", 
        "correct": "CACCBC", 
        "incorrect": "CACCBA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.6321077405478167, 
        "stimulus": 2151, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACCCC", 
        "correct": "ABCCC", 
        "incorrect": "AABCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8203370401098284, 
        "stimulus": 2515, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCACBABAB", 
        "correct": "BCCBBABAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCBABAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8202498743082542, 
        "stimulus": 2720, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCBACABBB", 
        "correct": "CCBCBBABBB", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCBABBBB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "AC=B", 
        "score": 0.8230859159606297, 
        "stimulus": 2538, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCCACAAA", 
        "correct": "CBCACACAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBABCACAAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7424262961901417, 
        "stimulus": 3972, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCB", 
        "correct": "ACAB", 
        "incorrect": "ACBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4663689526544408, 
        "stimulus": 3078, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCB", 
        "correct": "ACACB", 
        "incorrect": "AACBB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.46149418353985144, 
        "stimulus": 3458, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACBBCBB", 
        "correct": "CCACBCABB", 
        "incorrect": "CCACBABBB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7034671545210254, 
        "stimulus": 3170, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBC", 
        "correct": "CCA", 
        "incorrect": "CAB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4166666666666666, 
        "stimulus": 3057, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABC", 
        "correct": "ACA", 
        "incorrect": "AAB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7735947093724258, 
        "stimulus": 3080, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAB", 
        "correct": "CAAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5021838834590163, 
        "stimulus": 3086, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BC", 
        "correct": "CA", 
        "incorrect": "AB", 
        "length": 2, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5590169943749475, 
        "stimulus": 2997, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAABCCA", 
        "correct": "BAACACA", 
        "incorrect": "BAACCAA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.44144038613664666, 
        "stimulus": 3789, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCCBABCA", 
        "correct": "BCCCBACAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCCCBAABA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8747883341869791, 
        "stimulus": 3933, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCBACCA", 
        "correct": "BACABACCA", 
        "incorrect": "BAABBACCA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7330762418926623, 
        "stimulus": 3531, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACBAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBACBAA", 
        "correct": "CABACBAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBACBAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0393222961619026, 
        "stimulus": 3134, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBBB", 
        "correct": "CABBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7208894769912351, 
        "stimulus": 3541, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBC", 
        "correct": "ACCA", 
        "incorrect": "ACAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.28559350974064324, 
        "stimulus": 3199, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCCBC", 
        "correct": "ACCACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCACBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.48185897978868203, 
        "stimulus": 3101, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAACBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBCCAACBB", 
        "correct": "BBCACAACBB", 
        "incorrect": "BBABCAACBB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7039595188435077, 
        "stimulus": 3892, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABACC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCABACC", 
        "correct": "CCACABACC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCABACC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7674993794068353, 
        "stimulus": 3703, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBC", 
        "correct": "BBCA", 
        "incorrect": "BBAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.13807118745769836, 
        "stimulus": 3093, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABBCC", 
        "correct": "AABCAC", 
        "incorrect": "AABABC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4316624691168002, 
        "stimulus": 3094, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABCB", 
        "correct": "AACAB", 
        "incorrect": "AACBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4643543905251678, 
        "stimulus": 3416, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCBCBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCBCBBABC", 
        "correct": "ACCBCBBACA", 
        "incorrect": "ACCBCBBAAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0504690181338245, 
        "stimulus": 3184, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCCBAC", 
        "correct": "ABCACBAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABABCBAC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6182798528862479, 
        "stimulus": 3994, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCBABCACB", 
        "correct": "BCCBACAACB", 
        "incorrect": "BCCBAABACB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6884485429899387, 
        "stimulus": 3764, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCA", 
        "correct": "ACAA", 
        "incorrect": "AABA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3535533905932738, 
        "stimulus": 2999, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCA", 
        "correct": "CAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABA", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4653002578169966, 
        "stimulus": 3042, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBAA", 
        "correct": "CCABAA", 
        "incorrect": "CABBAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4885002959394329, 
        "stimulus": 3580, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCB", 
        "correct": "CABCB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7552515757944895, 
        "stimulus": 3200, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCB", 
        "correct": "BCAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3340114560999052, 
        "stimulus": 3023, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACABC", 
        "correct": "BACACA", 
        "incorrect": "BACAAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.082842712474619, 
        "stimulus": 3890, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBBCCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCBBCCC", 
        "correct": "CABCBBCCC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCBBCCC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0451779282435307, 
        "stimulus": 3688, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBA", 
        "correct": "CABA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7676910196190511, 
        "stimulus": 3016, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBC", 
        "correct": "ABCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8304749561582089, 
        "stimulus": 3625, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBCBB", 
        "correct": "CCBCABB", 
        "incorrect": "CCBABBB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6333120768037069, 
        "stimulus": 3776, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBABBABBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBBABBABBA", 
        "correct": "CABBABBABBA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBABBABBA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8447075858824656, 
        "stimulus": 3380, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCCBC", 
        "correct": "CCBCCCA", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCCAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5239785982543289, 
        "stimulus": 3760, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCB", 
        "correct": "CAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0513768205612355, 
        "stimulus": 3033, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBCC", 
        "correct": "ACABCC", 
        "incorrect": "AABCCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6678003464848266, 
        "stimulus": 3854, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCBAA", 
        "correct": "ACCABAA", 
        "incorrect": "ACABBAA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6447547683119937, 
        "stimulus": 3420, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACBCA", 
        "correct": "BACCAA", 
        "incorrect": "BACABA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4313483869534397, 
        "stimulus": 3695, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAC", 
        "correct": "CAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABAC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5021838834590163, 
        "stimulus": 3325, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACBACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBACABC", 
        "correct": "CACBACACA", 
        "incorrect": "CACBACAAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7719274017550141, 
        "stimulus": 3535, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABA", 
        "correct": "CAABA", 
        "incorrect": "ABABA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.47334621371327823, 
        "stimulus": 3475, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBB", 
        "correct": "CABB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3535533905932738, 
        "stimulus": 3018, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCBBCBBA", 
        "correct": "ABCABBCBBA", 
        "incorrect": "ABABBBCBBA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8176581116013114, 
        "stimulus": 3810, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCAABCAA", 
        "correct": "CCCAACAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CCCAAABAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6535797406902434, 
        "stimulus": 3190, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAACBBCAC", 
        "correct": "BAACBCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BAACBABAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.706634368962673, 
        "stimulus": 3902, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBACBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCABBACBB", 
        "correct": "ACAABBACBB", 
        "incorrect": "AABABBACBB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7064240376779557, 
        "stimulus": 3597, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCA", 
        "correct": "CCCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CCABA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.524663811869502, 
        "stimulus": 3293, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBCBA", 
        "correct": "ACABCBA", 
        "incorrect": "AABBCBA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8051571655425355, 
        "stimulus": 3103, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAAC", 
        "correct": "CAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACAAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7211102550927979, 
        "stimulus": 3942, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCC", 
        "correct": "CACAC", 
        "incorrect": "CACCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5598621539639147, 
        "stimulus": 3296, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBA", 
        "correct": "CCABA", 
        "incorrect": "CABBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.46563541420126753, 
        "stimulus": 3647, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCC", 
        "correct": "ABCAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABABC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5004047788941065, 
        "stimulus": 3169, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCBC", 
        "correct": "BCCCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCCAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.675, 
        "stimulus": 3362, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCA", 
        "correct": "BCAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6756949406396194, 
        "stimulus": 3133, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCA", 
        "correct": "ABCAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABABA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5416025603090641, 
        "stimulus": 3206, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBC", 
        "correct": "BCA", 
        "incorrect": "BAB", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6893365545799229, 
        "stimulus": 3009, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABABCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABABCBABCC", 
        "correct": "ABABCBACAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABABCBAABC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8590745892352369, 
        "stimulus": 3107, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABBC", 
        "correct": "BABCA", 
        "incorrect": "BABAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6848053251350587, 
        "stimulus": 3210, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAACA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCAAACA", 
        "correct": "CACAAACA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCAAACA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6631853547951846, 
        "stimulus": 3011, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCCBB", 
        "correct": "ABCACBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABABCBB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5300293599877083, 
        "stimulus": 3844, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCBAAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCBAAACBCC", 
        "correct": "ACCBAAACCAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACCBAAACABC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0167897505022845, 
        "stimulus": 3642, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCB", 
        "correct": "CBCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBABB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5251983752196245, 
        "stimulus": 3593, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAACBCBAC", 
        "correct": "ABAACCABAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABAACABBAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5361931698654246, 
        "stimulus": 3230, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABCBCB", 
        "correct": "BCABCCAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCABCABB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7249941355615502, 
        "stimulus": 3221, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACBCAA", 
        "correct": "CCACCAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CCACABAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.46085166730658494, 
        "stimulus": 3352, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCC", 
        "correct": "BCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.620987117418711, 
        "stimulus": 3121, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBCBCACAC", 
        "correct": "BBCBCCAACAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCBCABACAC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6484827407727711, 
        "stimulus": 3447, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBBABA", 
        "correct": "CABBABA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBABA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7628574772604939, 
        "stimulus": 3983, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCAA", 
        "correct": "ACACAA", 
        "incorrect": "BAACAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.38993310385905605, 
        "stimulus": 3767, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCCCC", 
        "correct": "BCACCC", 
        "incorrect": "BABCCC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.32520924713446997, 
        "stimulus": 3811, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCB", 
        "correct": "CACAB", 
        "incorrect": "CAABB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4163331998932265, 
        "stimulus": 3205, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCC", 
        "correct": "CAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABC", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0513768205612355, 
        "stimulus": 3000, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCCBC", 
        "correct": "CCCCCA", 
        "incorrect": "CCCCAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5034574339058885, 
        "stimulus": 3694, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBCBCCB", 
        "correct": "BBCABCCB", 
        "incorrect": "BBABBCCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7271999548178718, 
        "stimulus": 3895, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCABA", 
        "correct": "BCAABA", 
        "incorrect": "ACABBA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3912417183782253, 
        "stimulus": 3324, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABB", 
        "correct": "CAABB", 
        "incorrect": "ABABB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7804605365128273, 
        "stimulus": 3151, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABACC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABACC", 
        "correct": "CAABACC", 
        "incorrect": "ABABACC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.943762400884854, 
        "stimulus": 3492, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABC", 
        "correct": "BACA", 
        "incorrect": "BAAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3535533905932738, 
        "stimulus": 3074, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACABC", 
        "correct": "ACACA", 
        "incorrect": "ACAAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6893998226613031, 
        "stimulus": 3068, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCA", 
        "correct": "CCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CABA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4663689526544408, 
        "stimulus": 3063, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCABCBBB", 
        "correct": "CCBCACABBB", 
        "incorrect": "CCBCAABBBB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7781882616461572, 
        "stimulus": 3129, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBBCACAAA", 
        "correct": "ACBCAACAAA", 
        "incorrect": "ACABBACAAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4514847146996087, 
        "stimulus": 3474, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCABA", 
        "correct": "CCAABA", 
        "incorrect": "ACBABA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6626419755456955, 
        "stimulus": 3504, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBAAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCABBAAC", 
        "correct": "ACAABBAAC", 
        "incorrect": "AABABBAAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7872592721657464, 
        "stimulus": 3072, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAABBCC", 
        "correct": "BAABCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BAABABC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5100851218853983, 
        "stimulus": 3053, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBAB", 
        "correct": "CABAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABBAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6322037947028606, 
        "stimulus": 3514, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAAB", 
        "correct": "CAAAB", 
        "incorrect": "ACAAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7343111656761706, 
        "stimulus": 3829, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCBBBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBBBACBCA", 
        "correct": "CCCBBBACCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CCCBBBACABA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.96868334881353, 
        "stimulus": 3753, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAAA", 
        "correct": "CAAAA", 
        "incorrect": "ACAAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7211102550927979, 
        "stimulus": 3711, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCCA", 
        "correct": "CCACCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCACCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.2667968432263688, 
        "stimulus": 3082, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBCAAB", 
        "correct": "CBCCAAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABAAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6992270616612424, 
        "stimulus": 3436, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCABA", 
        "correct": "ACACABA", 
        "incorrect": "ACCAABA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3562004564546481, 
        "stimulus": 3001, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBBAB", 
        "correct": "BCABBAB", 
        "incorrect": "BABBBAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5053918463601752, 
        "stimulus": 3553, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCC", 
        "correct": "CACC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6013016321331407, 
        "stimulus": 2995, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACBBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACBCBACBBB", 
        "correct": "BACCABACBBB", 
        "incorrect": "BACABBACBBB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7426224575477105, 
        "stimulus": 3536, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCC", 
        "correct": "CABCC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.717824571525269, 
        "stimulus": 2996, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCAA", 
        "correct": "CACAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCAA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6110100926607788, 
        "stimulus": 3655, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCB", 
        "correct": "CCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CABB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4038902148009503, 
        "stimulus": 3374, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACABBCBAA", 
        "correct": "CACABCABAA", 
        "incorrect": "CACABABBAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4124368265386335, 
        "stimulus": 3502, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACACCBCB", 
        "correct": "AACACCCAB", 
        "incorrect": "AACACCABB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6850804752575442, 
        "stimulus": 3931, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAACB", 
        "correct": "CAAACB", 
        "incorrect": "ABAACB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.837347006039755, 
        "stimulus": 3273, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBABCA", 
        "correct": "CBCBACAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBAABA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.880783545182223, 
        "stimulus": 3376, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCBAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCBACBCC", 
        "correct": "ABBCBACCAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBCBACABC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.9052030806897519, 
        "stimulus": 3839, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCAAA", 
        "correct": "ACAAAA", 
        "incorrect": "AABAAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.32520924713447, 
        "stimulus": 3304, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBC", 
        "correct": "CCCA", 
        "incorrect": "CCAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.518713459248918, 
        "stimulus": 3005, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABBAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCBABBAB", 
        "correct": "BACABABBAB", 
        "incorrect": "BAABBABBAB", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6512225335661617, 
        "stimulus": 3519, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABC", 
        "correct": "CACA", 
        "incorrect": "CAAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5758156413349492, 
        "stimulus": 3269, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBBA", 
        "correct": "CABBA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6549491074376186, 
        "stimulus": 3135, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBBCA", 
        "correct": "CABBCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBCA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.722265692454783, 
        "stimulus": 3724, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBBCBBCA", 
        "correct": "BBBBCBCAA", 
        "incorrect": "BBBBCBABA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.1307917485221506, 
        "stimulus": 3408, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCB", 
        "correct": "CCACB", 
        "incorrect": "CABCB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5186119294167204, 
        "stimulus": 3618, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBCABCA", 
        "correct": "CACBCAABCA", 
        "incorrect": "CACBABABCA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5390574844963236, 
        "stimulus": 3008, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBB", 
        "correct": "CCABB", 
        "incorrect": "CABBB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6880738560947612, 
        "stimulus": 3529, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCB", 
        "correct": "BACAB", 
        "incorrect": "BAABB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3963226077411258, 
        "stimulus": 3544, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABCAC", 
        "correct": "AACAAC", 
        "incorrect": "AAABAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6570576635597749, 
        "stimulus": 3691, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCCABC", 
        "correct": "BBCCACA", 
        "incorrect": "BBCCAAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0677093198654142, 
        "stimulus": 3278, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCABC", 
        "correct": "CBCACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCAAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.9481079743700507, 
        "stimulus": 3914, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCBBB", 
        "correct": "CCACBBB", 
        "incorrect": "CABCBBB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4900150976432944, 
        "stimulus": 3276, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABAABCC", 
        "correct": "ABAACAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABAACCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5804270002969821, 
        "stimulus": 3883, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABAABB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCCCABAABB", 
        "correct": "BCACCABAABB", 
        "incorrect": "BABCCABAABB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.9920200522830193, 
        "stimulus": 3415, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCAC", 
        "correct": "BCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBAC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5138644160055224, 
        "stimulus": 3066, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABCCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCCCABCCC", 
        "correct": "BACACCABCCC", 
        "incorrect": "BACCACABCCC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8564294467209448, 
        "stimulus": 3305, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCBBCCAB", 
        "correct": "BCCBCACAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCCBABCAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6602493954820386, 
        "stimulus": 3787, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCABCABBBC", 
        "correct": "CCACAABBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CCAABABBBC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7431360514171403, 
        "stimulus": 3513, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBC", 
        "correct": "ACABC", 
        "incorrect": "AABBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5965176722724427, 
        "stimulus": 3062, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCACAC", 
        "correct": "CCAACAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABACAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4202313537886684, 
        "stimulus": 3191, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCABCCA", 
        "correct": "CBCACACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCACCAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.46091516498697493, 
        "stimulus": 3969, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AABBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABBBBCB", 
        "correct": "AABBBCAB", 
        "incorrect": "AABBBABB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.9052390641555984, 
        "stimulus": 3944, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCC", 
        "correct": "ACAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.1027742793115511, 
        "stimulus": 3241, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCBAB", 
        "correct": "BACABAB", 
        "incorrect": "BAABBAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6693918348079974, 
        "stimulus": 3155, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAA", 
        "correct": "CAAA", 
        "incorrect": "ABAA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3340114560999052, 
        "stimulus": 3007, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCBA", 
        "correct": "ACCABA", 
        "incorrect": "ACABBA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5146691774753243, 
        "stimulus": 3847, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABCC", 
        "correct": "AACAC", 
        "incorrect": "AACCA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5229202916708378, 
        "stimulus": 3238, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCAAB", 
        "correct": "BCAAAB", 
        "incorrect": "AABCAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7945636868276315, 
        "stimulus": 3806, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABCA", 
        "correct": "BCACAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCAABA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.46999504061951314, 
        "stimulus": 3984, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBC", 
        "correct": "CABCA", 
        "incorrect": "CABAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6601767440112786, 
        "stimulus": 3046, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCB", 
        "correct": "CACB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6719848605481964, 
        "stimulus": 3131, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBCBCBCC", 
        "correct": "BBCBCCABCC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCBCABBCC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7203755531054852, 
        "stimulus": 3816, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACBC", 
        "correct": "BACCA", 
        "incorrect": "BACAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6088705155477337, 
        "stimulus": 3231, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CAAACBCABBC", 
        "correct": "CAAACCAABBC", 
        "incorrect": "CAAACABABBC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4361065513754648, 
        "stimulus": 3159, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAABCBB", 
        "correct": "AAACABB", 
        "incorrect": "AAACBAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5994922408417861, 
        "stimulus": 3041, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABC", 
        "correct": "CAABC", 
        "incorrect": "ABABC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8071296880510179, 
        "stimulus": 3026, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        11, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        11, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAACBAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAACBAACBC", 
        "correct": "ACAACBAACCA", 
        "incorrect": "ACAACBAACAB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.2228661719247724, 
        "stimulus": 3763, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCAAAC", 
        "correct": "CAAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACAAAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8036818231174921, 
        "stimulus": 3716, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCA", 
        "correct": "CACA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCA", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7676910196190511, 
        "stimulus": 3034, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABC", 
        "correct": "BCACA", 
        "incorrect": "BCAAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.605439210851673, 
        "stimulus": 3486, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCCA", 
        "correct": "ACACCA", 
        "incorrect": "ACCACA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7012339934147575, 
        "stimulus": 3878, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACCBCCABCAC", 
        "correct": "ACCCACABCAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACACBCABCAC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5366893977722889, 
        "stimulus": 3700, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACBBC", 
        "correct": "CAACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABACBBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7651417735358972, 
        "stimulus": 3624, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBBC", 
        "correct": "ABBCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8297527242096489, 
        "stimulus": 3340, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCBCACAB", 
        "correct": "BCCCAACAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCCABACAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.43412498911354946, 
        "stimulus": 3419, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        11, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        11, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACCBBBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACCBBBCABC", 
        "correct": "AACCBBBCACA", 
        "incorrect": "AACCBBBCAAB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.3754523881885525, 
        "stimulus": 3428, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCA", 
        "correct": "BCCAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCABA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7376019509442044, 
        "stimulus": 3217, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACABCA", 
        "correct": "ACACAA", 
        "incorrect": "ACAABA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5134838226259789, 
        "stimulus": 3306, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBBBBC", 
        "correct": "BCBBBCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBBBAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8229184283484975, 
        "stimulus": 3264, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCAAA", 
        "correct": "CCAAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CABAAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6009252125773316, 
        "stimulus": 3021, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBBCCBB", 
        "correct": "CCBCACBB", 
        "incorrect": "CCBABCBB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6400139987786073, 
        "stimulus": 3456, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBCCBCAB", 
        "correct": "BBCACBCAB", 
        "incorrect": "BBABCBCAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5202997266533547, 
        "stimulus": 3245, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBCBC", 
        "correct": "ABCBCCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBCAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.813823490364703, 
        "stimulus": 3020, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAACBBCA", 
        "correct": "AAACBCAA", 
        "incorrect": "AAACBABA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8709356897475288, 
        "stimulus": 3182, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCBBB", 
        "correct": "CACBBB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBBB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6065590096598569, 
        "stimulus": 3791, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBCBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCBBABCA", 
        "correct": "BCBCBBACAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCBBAABA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8702754568103022, 
        "stimulus": 3565, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCCBCAA", 
        "correct": "BBCCCAAA", 
        "incorrect": "BBCCABAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.338501600193165, 
        "stimulus": 3754, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACCBAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCACCBAAA", 
        "correct": "CCAACCBAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CABACCBAAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.9237264009601106, 
        "stimulus": 3321, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBACA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBBACA", 
        "correct": "CABBACA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBACA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8561921452970095, 
        "stimulus": 3448, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AACBBCA", 
        "correct": "AACBCAA", 
        "incorrect": "AACBABA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8647233071213164, 
        "stimulus": 3636, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABBACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABBACBBCAA", 
        "correct": "BABBACBCAAA", 
        "incorrect": "BABBACBABAA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.9045675816214688, 
        "stimulus": 3960, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBABCBC", 
        "correct": "CBBACABC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBAABBC", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6562715467372069, 
        "stimulus": 3820, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCBBBCB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCCBBBCB", 
        "correct": "CACCBBBCB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCBBBCB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8887188055234975, 
        "stimulus": 3460, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCCBCBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBCCCBCBA", 
        "correct": "BCABCCCBCBA", 
        "incorrect": "BABBCCCBCBA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.9070467032239719, 
        "stimulus": 3249, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABBCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBCCCABBCA", 
        "correct": "BBCACCABBCA", 
        "incorrect": "BBABCCABBCA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7881064640802073, 
        "stimulus": 3858, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCAB", 
        "correct": "BCCAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BCABAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4183807356913426, 
        "stimulus": 3413, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBBC", 
        "correct": "ACABBC", 
        "incorrect": "AABBBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.23570226039551587, 
        "stimulus": 3038, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCCC", 
        "correct": "CACCC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.31927853381037496, 
        "stimulus": 3472, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCC", 
        "correct": "BCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BCABC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7642359832124476, 
        "stimulus": 3350, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBBBC", 
        "correct": "CBCBBCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBBAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.912875780729823, 
        "stimulus": 3144, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCBAAB", 
        "correct": "CACABAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CAABBAAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7987565354980215, 
        "stimulus": 3831, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBAABCCA", 
        "correct": "BBAACACA", 
        "incorrect": "BBAACCAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7104622562200429, 
        "stimulus": 3516, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCBC", 
        "correct": "CACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7068572101106673, 
        "stimulus": 3768, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBC", 
        "correct": "BCCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5689679266916002, 
        "stimulus": 3143, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCACBBCAC", 
        "correct": "CCACBCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCACBABAC", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4690925228348049, 
        "stimulus": 3252, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBCAAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBCBCAAC", 
        "correct": "BCABCBCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BABBCBCAAC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.9230860901293104, 
        "stimulus": 3684, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCCBC", 
        "correct": "CACACBC", 
        "incorrect": "CAACBBC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6257266231544876, 
        "stimulus": 3414, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCABB", 
        "correct": "ACACABB", 
        "incorrect": "ACCAABB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6374399731643404, 
        "stimulus": 3207, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBC", 
        "correct": "CBCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBAB", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7071067811865476, 
        "stimulus": 3138, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBBC", 
        "correct": "CABBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABBBC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7068572101106673, 
        "stimulus": 3116, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCA", 
        "correct": "ACCAA", 
        "incorrect": "ACABA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3651483716701108, 
        "stimulus": 3183, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCAABC", 
        "correct": "BBCAACA", 
        "incorrect": "BBCAAAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0810433529879357, 
        "stimulus": 3790, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCAAAC", 
        "correct": "CCAAAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABAAAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3355052540724273, 
        "stimulus": 3330, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBCBACA", 
        "correct": "CBCCABACA", 
        "incorrect": "CBCABBACA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7172010431804777, 
        "stimulus": 3234, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCBCC", 
        "correct": "CCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CCABC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.47849590733185315, 
        "stimulus": 3582, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACAACABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCACAACABA", 
        "correct": "CACACAACABA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCACAACABA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.9749220760695254, 
        "stimulus": 3922, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCA", 
        "correct": "CBCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CABBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6800382212693811, 
        "stimulus": 3728, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCCB", 
        "correct": "ACCACB", 
        "incorrect": "ACABCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5001292288530882, 
        "stimulus": 3172, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBAABCCBC", 
        "correct": "ACBAACACBC", 
        "incorrect": "ACBAACCABC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.682767970835817, 
        "stimulus": 3126, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCCCCB", 
        "correct": "CBCACCCB", 
        "incorrect": "CBCCACCB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.401448742751607, 
        "stimulus": 3076, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCCAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCABCCAB", 
        "correct": "CAABCCAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABABCCAB", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7603453162872774, 
        "stimulus": 3392, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCCAB", 
        "correct": "CACCAB", 
        "incorrect": "CCACAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8111644814969393, 
        "stimulus": 3880, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABCCB", 
        "correct": "CBACACB", 
        "incorrect": "CBACCAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5968133916810143, 
        "stimulus": 3142, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCC", 
        "correct": "CCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABC", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3535533905932738, 
        "stimulus": 3019, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AABCAA", 
        "correct": "AACAAA", 
        "incorrect": "AAABAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.32520924713446997, 
        "stimulus": 3572, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBAAAA", 
        "correct": "BCABAAAA", 
        "incorrect": "BABBAAAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.125, 
        "stimulus": 3615, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CACB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CACBBC", 
        "correct": "CACBCA", 
        "incorrect": "CACBAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0837444829465217, 
        "stimulus": 3780, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBCAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCCBBCAA", 
        "correct": "CBCACBBCAA", 
        "incorrect": "CBABCBBCAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8698004643846788, 
        "stimulus": 3247, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAABCB", 
        "correct": "BAACAB", 
        "incorrect": "BAAABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6974262796402785, 
        "stimulus": 3731, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCABCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCABCABCBC", 
        "correct": "CCABCACABC", 
        "incorrect": "CCABCAABBC", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8922005290381345, 
        "stimulus": 3648, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBABABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABABBBC", 
        "correct": "CBABABBCA", 
        "incorrect": "CBABABBAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0197689338605957, 
        "stimulus": 3180, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACB", 
        "correct": "CAACB", 
        "incorrect": "ABACB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5033222956847166, 
        "stimulus": 3246, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCACC", 
        "correct": "CAACC", 
        "incorrect": "ABACC", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8012385614704423, 
        "stimulus": 3056, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCBBC", 
        "correct": "CACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "ABCBBC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6159002557225597, 
        "stimulus": 3939, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAAABCA", 
        "correct": "AAAACAA", 
        "incorrect": "AAABAAA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.43409605226176595, 
        "stimulus": 3610, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBA", 
        "correct": "ACABA", 
        "incorrect": "AABBA", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6644321125232455, 
        "stimulus": 3842, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCCA", 
        "correct": "CACACA", 
        "incorrect": "CACCAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5997805839356698, 
        "stimulus": 3845, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCCBC", 
        "correct": "BCCCCA", 
        "incorrect": "BCCCAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3417309546287457, 
        "stimulus": 3100, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCAB", 
        "correct": "CACAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CAABAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.645597329780608, 
        "stimulus": 3333, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAABB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCAABB", 
        "correct": "CACAABB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCAABB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8425790505369306, 
        "stimulus": 3773, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBCAB", 
        "correct": "CCCCAAB", 
        "incorrect": "CCCABAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.36943144402816425, 
        "stimulus": 3032, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABBCBCA", 
        "correct": "BABCABCA", 
        "incorrect": "BAABBBCA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4232601666027447, 
        "stimulus": 3957, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCBCA", 
        "correct": "BBCCAA", 
        "incorrect": "BBCABA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4348498450673544, 
        "stimulus": 3438, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACAABCC", 
        "correct": "ACAACAC", 
        "incorrect": "ACAACCA", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.788382970151383, 
        "stimulus": 3510, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCCACBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCCACBABBCA", 
        "correct": "BCCACBABCAA", 
        "incorrect": "BCCACBABABA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.1361416631860604, 
        "stimulus": 3650, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBACBAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCCBACBAAA", 
        "correct": "BCACBACBAAA", 
        "incorrect": "BABCBACBAAA", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0754889030121004, 
        "stimulus": 3377, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BACC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BACCBC", 
        "correct": "BACCCA", 
        "incorrect": "BACCAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8735258476213427, 
        "stimulus": 3732, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AAA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "AAABCA", 
        "correct": "AAACAA", 
        "incorrect": "AABAAA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.3004626062886657, 
        "stimulus": 3051, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBAC", 
        "correct": "ACABAC", 
        "incorrect": "AABBAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7715614990845272, 
        "stimulus": 3897, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBBCBCC", 
        "correct": "CBBCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBBCABC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6631350463417303, 
        "stimulus": 3319, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAAC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCAAC", 
        "correct": "CCACAAC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCAAC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5431037973480554, 
        "stimulus": 3749, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBCAB", 
        "correct": "BBCAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BBCABA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4261675240134347, 
        "stimulus": 3935, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBABCB", 
        "correct": "CBACAB", 
        "incorrect": "CBAABB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6823113268054192, 
        "stimulus": 3149, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBC", 
        "correct": "ABCCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCAB", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7285075872654746, 
        "stimulus": 3248, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAAC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BAACBCC", 
        "correct": "BAACCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BAACABC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.826626124148895, 
        "stimulus": 3591, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCBBCC", 
        "correct": "CBCBCAC", 
        "incorrect": "CBCBABC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6333120768037068, 
        "stimulus": 3918, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBCBAA", 
        "correct": "ACABCBAA", 
        "incorrect": "AABBCBAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4564354645876384, 
        "stimulus": 3508, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBBC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCABCCBBC", 
        "correct": "CABCACACBBC", 
        "incorrect": "CABCACCABBC", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5542298080775407, 
        "stimulus": 3154, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBCBB", 
        "correct": "ABCABB", 
        "incorrect": "ABABCB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.38169570337812847, 
        "stimulus": 3394, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBCCAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCCBCCAAA", 
        "correct": "CCACBCCAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CABCBCCAAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8360830825995857, 
        "stimulus": 3236, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACAAAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCACAAAA", 
        "correct": "ACAACAAAA", 
        "incorrect": "AABACAAAA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7868252336334431, 
        "stimulus": 3124, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CBCABCC", 
        "correct": "CCAABCC", 
        "incorrect": "CABABCC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6060772959876477, 
        "stimulus": 3900, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBABCCA", 
        "correct": "ABBACACA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBACCAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.633735252586102, 
        "stimulus": 3052, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBCCBCC", 
        "correct": "BBCCCAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCCABC", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6575697371257845, 
        "stimulus": 3117, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBCAC", 
        "correct": "BBCAAC", 
        "incorrect": "BBCACA", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5437544797427997, 
        "stimulus": 3444, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBCAAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABCABBCAAB", 
        "correct": "BACAABBCAAB", 
        "incorrect": "BAABABBCAAB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7332742431740523, 
        "stimulus": 3291, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCAACACB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCBCAACACB", 
        "correct": "ACABCAACACB", 
        "incorrect": "AABBCAACACB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.8767561353345728, 
        "stimulus": 3031, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BABABCBA", 
        "correct": "BABACABA", 
        "incorrect": "BABAABBA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6528548698850175, 
        "stimulus": 3208, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBAABA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBAABABC", 
        "correct": "ACBAABACA", 
        "incorrect": "ACBAABAAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.0687700941787552, 
        "stimulus": 3609, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CC"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABCCC", 
        "correct": "CACACC", 
        "incorrect": "CACCAC", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4262918873760447, 
        "stimulus": 3817, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABBA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBABC", 
        "correct": "ABBACA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBAAB", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.4426706481858205, 
        "stimulus": 3865, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BCBCBCA"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BCBCBCABC", 
        "correct": "BCBCBCACA", 
        "incorrect": "BCBCBCAAB", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.186795803223698, 
        "stimulus": 3697, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ACBAB"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCBCACBAB", 
        "correct": "ABCCCAACBAB", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCABACBAB", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5095704933278274, 
        "stimulus": 3742, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBBAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "BBBABBCCBA", 
        "correct": "BBBABCACBA", 
        "incorrect": "BBBABABCBA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6177908669401093, 
        "stimulus": 3527, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CCCBBB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CCCBBBBCAA", 
        "correct": "CCCBBBCAAA", 
        "incorrect": "CCCBBBCBAA", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 1.079993707751852, 
        "stimulus": 3393, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BBCBA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "AC"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ACBCBBCBA", 
        "correct": "ACCABBCBA", 
        "incorrect": "ACABBBCBA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7365126706534777, 
        "stimulus": 3251, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CABA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABBBCCABA", 
        "correct": "ABBCACABA", 
        "incorrect": "ABBABCABA", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.6854349825410955, 
        "stimulus": 3961, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "ABCCB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "ABCCBBC", 
        "correct": "ABCCBCA", 
        "incorrect": "ABCCBAB", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.7977858997080127, 
        "stimulus": 3239, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "A"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "C"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "B"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "BAA"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "CAB"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "CABBCBAA", 
        "correct": "CABCABAA", 
        "incorrect": "CABABBAA", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "BC=CA", 
        "score": 0.5398942690557654, 
        "stimulus": 3483, 
        "system": "BINARY"
    }
]